<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE aoCars [
<!ELEMENT aoCars (car)*>
<!ELEMENT car ANY>
<!ATTLIST car id ID #REQUIRED>
<!ATTLIST car price CDATA #REQUIRED>
]>
<aoCars>
  <car id="_16798977" price="32000">This is an Acura, info set from XML!</car>
  <car id="_33570817" price="44550">This is an award winning AMX that features a nut-and-bolt restoration that utilizes many N.O.S. parts. Among the new old stock parts are rocker moldings, deck lid, rear valance, front fenders, grille, hood molding, headlight bezels, parking lights/turn signal lenses and housings, all side marker lamps, door latches and strikers, door seals, jamb bumpers, trunk seal, outer door handles with correct finish, gas tank, bolts and sending unit, along with many other components and trim details.  This is a very well-equipped example that is finished in Bayshore Blue with a black interior; among the features are tilt steering wheel, center armrest and cushion (“buddy seat”), AM/FM radio, Light Group, Visibility Group, optional 15-inch Machine wheels, tinted glass, air conditioning, front spoiler, black rally stripes, black vinyl bucket seats, Go Package, space-saver spare, dual mirrors with driver’s side remote; power steering and brakes. The engine is a 390-cid, 325-hp V-8 that is mated to a four-speed manual transmission.  This fine AMX has placed first at the Hoosier Auto Show in Indianapolis in both 2003 and 2004. A first place was also won by this AMC at a Cincinnati concours d’elegance in 2005. It has also won the First Junior Award at the AACA spring meet, and that fall, it won the AACA Senior Award at the prestigious and largely attended Hershey meet. In 2012 it won the AACA Grand National Award in Tennessee. As recently as 2013, it obtained the AACA top honor by winning the Senior Grand National Award in Moline, Illinois.   The vendor does state that the original 360-cid engine was replaced with this correct, rebuilt 390-cid version that was optional to the car in 1970. The Bayshore Blue paint is also original spec for this 1970 model; it has been applied to replace the original Glen Green.</car>
  <car id="_50331649" price="126500">The 1906 American Tourist was the first production automobile designed by Harry C. Stutz. Its Stutz-designed side-valve four-cylinder 336 cubic inch engine broke no new ground, but equally showed Stutz's appreciation for the desirable attributes of touring car engines, in this case a practical operating range of 125- to 1,450-rpm. Live axle suspension with semi-elliptical leaf springs and platform rear suspension with a semi-elliptical cross spring were characteristic of the highest quality automobiles of the day. Harry Stutz's Tourist showed its value, quality and practicality by earning its place in the American model lineup from its inception in 1906 until 1913, just a year before American ceased production in 1914. The Stutz-designed four-cylinder engine powered all automobiles built by American Motor Cars until 1913. American built some 45,000 automobiles in just 9 years, double the production of Packards in the same period. This 1906 American Tourist Roi des Belges Touring was restored years ago for one of the founders of car collecting in America, Dr. Samuel Scher. It is one of very few surviving examples of its model, a nearly unique example of an important milestone in both the evolution of the American automobile and in the development of Harry Stutz's experience and his concepts of automobile design. Finished in red with black mudguards, it has red leather upholstery and a black cloth top. The American eagle mascot spreads its wings proudly on the radiator cap. There are Rushmore acetylene headlights, Gray & Davis kerosene sidelights, a magnificent Rushmore swivel-mounted acetylene searchlight on the cowl, Stewart speedometer and a brass bulb horn. The thoroughness of its restoration and the care it's had in the last two generations are reflected in the set of side curtains that still accompany it. One of the great automobiles of early American history, it will still show its heels to traffic with style and panache that is almost unknown today.</car>
  <car id="_67124481" price="47300">It’s a car. It’s a boat. Actually, it’s both. Nothing draws a crowd like an Amphicar. Developed in West Germany, the Amphicar was aimed squarely at America’s leisure market and debuted at the 1961 New York Auto Show. As the culmination of a 15-year, $25 million development program, the Amphicar was conceived by amphibious-vehicle pioneer Hans Trippel. A curious fusion of road-going and aquatic transport, it remains particularly popular as a unique and eye-catching collector’s item with its amphibious design and twin-screw propellers. Powered by a 1,147-cc Triumph Herald inline four-cylinder engine mated to a four-speed manual transmission, it directed power to the rear wheels on land and, once on water, to twin propellers at the rear. This Amphicar is finished in Beach White and features a black soft-top, red steel wheels and chrome hubcaps, whitewall tires, red and white two-tone upholstery. Amphicar marketing highlighted the vehicle’s ease of operation, and its unofficial “770” designation referred to its factory-claimed top speeds of seven knots on water and 70-mph on land. It is generally agreed that 3,878 were built through 1967, with the majority exported to the USA, far fewer are thought to remain.</car>
  <car id="_83910657" price="52250">The Aston Martin DB7 was launched in March 1993 at the Geneva Motor Show and marked the return of the six-cylinder Aston Martin. Penned by Ian Callum, the rakish lines of the DB7 were beautiful, hearkening back to iconic models from the sixties. Although it was originally intended to be an "entry level" Aston Martin, it quickly evolved into much more.  In 1999 Aston Martin squeezed its first production 12-cylinder engine into the DB7 to create the potent DB7 Vantage. The Aston Martin DB7 is a Grand Touring car in the finest tradition. Produced from 1994 to 2004, the DB7 proved to be one of the most popular Aston Martin models.  For those seeking employment as an international spy, there is really only one marque of automobile for daily transportation needs, the heralded name of Aston Martin. This DB7 nicely fits the bill with a well-trimmed black leather interior that is fully loaded with all of the accouterment required for sports car motoring. Aside from very light wear to the driver-side seat bolster and a high-end Alpine entertainment system, this low-mile Vantage appears like new from the inside. On the Titanium Silver exterior, no obvious blemishes are to be found on the soft folding top or the paint and trim. It is fitted with 19-inch alloy rims wrapped with Yokohama rubber. The 5.9-liter, 420 horsepower V-12 and five-speed transmission with steering shift will ensure great performance on the next mission.</car>
  <car id="_100670977" price="145750">The beautiful supercharged 852 Phaeton Sedan offered here has been driven and enjoyed by its owner, an enthusiastic Auburn, Indiana resident, on several regional ACD Club tours. Reliability has been excellent, and the car runs beautifully and performs well at highway speeds, with the optional “Dual Ratio” rear axle functioning properly, as confirmed by recent road testing by an Auctions America specialist. No less beautiful cosmetically, it is in “high-end driver” condition, with excellent chrome, interior, and top, and only slight age showing to the rich green paint.   The tan leather interior is an attractive complement to the body tone and features elegant instrumentation with a damascene-type dashboard. The exterior exhaust pipes and optional sidemounted spare with cover add sportiness and style. Chrome headlights and factory installed trunk were both optional equipment in 1935. The trunk adds 13.5-cubic feet of luggage space. Wire wheels, whitewall tires, dual mirrors, chrome taillights and vacuum windshield wipers are all part of this desirable platform. It will continue to be an outstanding tour car and welcome at ACD Club events. The Auburn has been certified by the Auburn-Cord-Duesenberg Club as a Category No. 1, Certified Original Car. It is also one of the most drivable and enjoyable of all Full Classics, as recognized by the CCCA.  Introduced in 1935, the all-new 851 featured beautiful Gordon Buehrig-penned styling and offered an optional Switzer-Cummins centrifugal supercharger, which boosted output by 30 percent to 150-hp. Developed by Kurt Beier at Schwitzer-Cummins and adapted to the Auburn-Lycoming inline eight-cylinder engine by Augie Duesenberg and Pearl Watson, the supercharger ran at six times engine speed and generated useful boost from 2,000-rpm upwards.   The Auburn 852 was the last hurrah for the Auburn Automobile Company. As was the case with many of the independent manufacturers, their final products were often among their best. The styling, introduced in 1935, was the last Gordon Buehrig designed Auburn line to see production.   Established in 1903, the Auburn Automobile Company matured into a well-respected builder of reliable cars, but it was not until E.L. Cord assumed the company’s presidency in 1924 that its market stature grew. In fact, as the once-buoyant auto market collapsed following Black Tuesday, Auburn’s sales continued to increase. By 1931, Auburn was the 13th largest American automaker, but the triumph was short-lived, as sales fell drastically in 1932 and 1933.</car>
  <car id="_117464577" price="64900">In March 1995 at the Geneva Motor Show, Rolls-Royce Motors unveiled its convertible version of the Continental R, the Bentley Azure. Now considered a modern classic, the Pininfarina-designed Azure is acknowledged by Rolls-Royce and Bentley enthusiasts to be one of the most desirable cars ever built. The two-door open tourer seats four adults in sumptuous comfort, thanks in part to its brilliant computer-controlled automatic ride control. Whether enjoying a leisurely top-down Sunday drive or covering great distances at speed and experiencing the thrill of putting the car through its paces, the well-mannered Azure is the definitive driver’s car. This 2000 Azure convertible has covered only 26,000 miles from new and is beautifully presented in rich black body color; accented with matching red-piped black leather upholstery and a black cloth top. It has Bentley embroidered headrests, tinted glass, and two matching Bentley umbrellas in the trunk, as well as all the standard luxury conveniences expected of a Bentley. It is in exceptionally clean and well maintained condition consistent with the low recorded mileage. Boosted by a Garrett turbocharger the big 6.75-liter V-8 delivers 400 brake horsepower and 590-lb/ft of torque. The limited production Azure convertible was as dominant on the road as its luxury and exclusivity dominated the boulevards of resorts and spas. Priced in excess of $300,000 when new, it is an automobile to be proud to own and drive. Only 1,308 units were built until production ended in 2003. In that time, just 709 Azures were exported to the U.S. market.</car>
  <car id="_134230529" price="42900">When BMW undertook the manufacturing of Renzo Rivolta’s Isetta in 1955, the firm incorporated some changes. The drivetrain was redesigned to use their 247 cubic centimeter four-cycle motorcycle engine. The gearbox output was coupled to a shaft through a rubber universal joint, which led, through another rubber joint, to the chain case. Inside were double drive chains running in oil to the solid rear axle. This arrangement made the whole power unit much quieter and reduced vibration. In fact, so much of the car was re-engineered that no earlier Iso parts were used, nor were they interchangeable. The front suspension was also reconfigured to a swing arm arrangement. Changes to the body included raising the headlights above the fenders so that they attached directly to the body. As with this car, in 1956 the engine displacement was increased to 297 cubic centimeters and compression was raised to achieve 13 horsepower. Although top speed did not increase from 53-mph, there was a marked increase in much-welcome torque, which helped on hills. More than 161,000 Isettas were built through 1962, along with some 34,000 BMW 600s, an elongated, four-passenger version with a flat-twin engine and a conventional rear axle. This rare example of a surviving European bubble window Isetta has the highly desirable “Z mold trim” and two-tone paint. It is the recipient of an excellent restoration and is very attractive in red and white; it has primarily red tartan upholstery and a black fabric sunroof. Very well detailed with front vent windows, dual mirrors, luggage rack and whitewall tires, it is an excellent example of the popular European microcar.</car>
  <car id="_134242049" price="98450">The Z8 is BMW’s spiritual successor to the 1950s 507 roadster. Both cars use a long hood with short deck design to create a powerful and sporty appearance. This limited production roadster with optional hardtop is equipped with a 4.9-liter DOHC V-8 as used in the M5, mated to a proper six-speed manual gearbox and producing nearly 400-hp. The Z8 has electronic traction control and four-wheel ventilated disc brakes with ABS and factory alloy wheels. This example has less than 51,000 miles and is handsomely presented in Titanium Silver Metallic with a black leather interior. The removable hardtop is in the same color as the body and has a rear window defogger. The soft-top is black and the remote mirrors are chrome. Luxury appointments are also prominent; these include alloy and leather interior trim elements, air conditioning, AM/FM/CD, Xenon lighting, fixed hoop rollover protection; power seats, door locks, windows, steering and brakes.  In developing the Z8, BMW married form and function like never before. The design is flawless from any angle, inside and out, carried over from Henrik Fisker’s Z07 concept introduced at Tokyo in 1997 and paying homage to the Count Albrecht Goertz-designed 507 of the 1950s with side vents, a sleek front end and such retro touches as a banjo-type steering wheel.  With 50/50 weight distribution and the acceleration of a Ferrari 360 Modena, this was BMW’s fastest roadster to date, the movie car choice of James Bond and a true supercar with brilliant braking and cornering. Motor Trend magazine brought out its true “M” potential, achieving a 0- to 60-mph sprint of just 4.2 seconds, and top speed was reported as 155-mph.</car>
  <car id="_151005953" price="56100">In 1949, this was Buick’s glamorous way to go places – with its top up or down it was one of the sharpest cars on any boulevard. Motoring thrills are gathered by its behavior on the road, wide seating and ease of having standard equipment such as the automatically-operated top, front seat and windows. This wonderful car has been restored from top-to-bottom starting with a solid, rust-free southern car that was one family owned for 50 years. The restoration process utilized mainly N.O.S. parts. The car has received new paint, interior, top, chrome, wiring and mechanicals; including new brakes, engine rebuild, transmission rebuild – even the factory radio has been refurbished and is in perfect working condition. The Sequoia Cream finish is handsomely matched with a low-profile black soft-top that has red piping, and the interior is upholstered in red vinyl. The engine is a factory original Fireball 248-cid, 115-hp straight eight-cylinder and the transmission is automatic. Among the features found on the Buick are “VentiPorts,” AM radio, clock, backup lights, fender skirts, bumper guards with accessory bar, distinguishing brightwork, red steel wheels with factory wheel covers and wide whitewall tires. This is a quite uncommon and sought-after Buick that has an iconic status and is presented in a meticulous fashion.</car>
  <car id="_151011841" price="13200">First introduced as a personal luxury car, Buick took their Riviera, offered bigger engine displacement, and the “Gentleman’s Musclecar” was born. Over 1.1 million Riveras were produced from 1963 to 1999, and perhaps the most memorable versions were the early seventies’ boattail styles seen from 1971-1973. Seen here, this two-tone green Riviera has the big 455 cubic inch engine topped with a four-barrel carburetor. The engine compartment is loaded with goodies such as power steering and brakes, as well as air conditioning. The interior is in remarkably well-preserved condition with medium green cloth fabrics and matching door panels and dash. The odometer shows 30,462 miles; perhaps giving reason for the fine original quality throughout. It also features cruise control, power windows and power seat. This is a prime example of Buick’s successful, powerful and memorable boattail Riviera.</car>
  <car id="_151015681" price="16500">Buick’s Grand National was menacing right out of the box. Most were black, with blackout trim. The interior was finished in a plethora of gray tones and fabrics, and the instrumentation included a tach and a boost gauge. Naturally, the suspension got stiffer springs and anti-roll bars, plus Goodyear radials on special aluminum wheels. Buick continued development on the GN package, and soon came an intercooler, along with 235 horsepower for 1986, then 245 horses in ’87. This black Buick shows only 40,000 miles from new and still wears its original paint. The two-tone cloth interior is in excellent condition and features an automatic transmission, power locks and windows, air conditioning, AM/FM/cassette and tilt wheel. The 3.8 turbo V-6 engine compartment is also detailed to appear as new.</car>
  <car id="_167784961" price="73700">Named Biarritz, the 1956 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible carried a substantial factory price tag of $6,501 when new. With only 2,150 examples built, this Biarritz is truly a masterpiece of Cadillac craftsmanship. It is difficult to find a better example of GM's styling and engineering prowess than viewing the 1956 Cadillac Eldorado. Surviving examples remain highly sought-after today and they continue to rank among the most luxurious and elegant automobiles ever to come from GM during the fabulous 1950s. For the first time, the Eldorado also had a hardtop model that was named the Seville.  This Eldorado is finished in Black with a black convertible top and a classly black and white two-tone interior. It is equipped with gold-finished Saber-Spoke wheels, wide whitewall tires, radio, clock; power top, seat, windows, steering and brakes, plus all the other inherent Eldorado features for 1956. The 1956 Cadillac is powered by a twin-carb 365-cid V-8 engine with 305-hp and is connected to a Hydra-Matic automatic transmission. This power equipment was standard in period for this model.</car>
  <car id="_167785217" price="181500">In 1957 Dwight Eisenhower was in the White House, Sputnik orbited planet Earth and Elvis Presley appeared on the Ed Sullivan show for the third and what would be last time. Presley also owned a new 1957 Cadillac Eldorado Biarritz, the car that marked the pinnacle of automotive ownership for many Americans. At over $7,000, it was achievable for the individual who had attained personal success. Someone like Elvis, climbing their way up the ladder and had the desire to reward themselves with the best that money could buy. It spoke to that success with vast amounts of chrome, impressive highway-devouring performance, and styling that only Harley Earl's studio could have dreamt up.</car>
  <car id="_184561665" price="28200">Running a 350-cid V-8 engine and a turbo 350 automatic transmission, this Bel Air wagon is presented in light blue with a white roof that has been intentionally aged to show patina and give it a rat rod style. The Chevy has front and rear Air Ride Technologies suspension, dual exhaust, polished aluminum American Racing wheels, power steering and power brakes.</car>
  <car id="_184561921" price="48400">While this Chevy truck displays many original attributes, it has been refurbished by A-Car Restorations of Reedsville, Wisconsin using a 350-cid V-8 General Motors crate engine that is matched to a floor-shift five-speed manual transmission. The rear end is a nine-inch Ford unit. The truck is very nicely presented in Viper Red and has a tan interior with a black tonneau cover. The steel wheels are color-keyed and have been mounted with wide whitewalls and are fit with chrome hubcaps and trim rings. Heidts front suspension, stainless steel exhaust, stereo; power steering and brakes are other features on this fine looking 1955 3100 truck.</car>
  <car id="_184561922" price="57200">The Tri-Five years from Chevrolet have always been favored 1950s American classics. This 1955 Bel Air is shown in Skyline Blue with India Ivory and beautiful two-tone slate blue upholstery. The interior is very well-restored with great attention to fit and finish of each component. It is powered by a 265 V-8 with a three-speed manual overdrive transmission. The engine bay is highlighted with chrome valve covers and has been detailed to better than factory standards. The underside of the chassis is equally detailed and impressive. Four new Coker wide whitewall radials have been mounted onto the correct steel wheels. The car also has full wheel covers, fender skirts, dual exhaust, dual external mirrors, tinted windshield, power top, original radio and clock, plus front and rear bumper guards. This is a prime opportunity to forego the time and cost of a restoration and to simply purchase a fully restored Bel Air.</car>
  <car id="_184561923" price="101200">This custom Bel Air has received a total frame-off restoration that includes extensive new sheetmetal. The chassis is from Custom Progressive and is powder-coated in blue that matches the body color. It is powered by a fuel-injected GM LS2 6.0-liter V-8 that is dyno’d at 507 horsepower at the rear wheels. Along with a custom cam, the engine has a Magnuson supercharger with 40-pound injectors and custom intercooler with a remote custom tank. The transmission is a T-56 six-speed manual that has a hydraulic clutch system. Other mechanical workings consist of C4 Corvette front suspension components and narrowed Dana 44 rear end, also from a C4. The power brakes are hydraulic and by Hydratech with 12-inch Wilwood brake rotors and four-piston calipers. The custom radiator has custom computer-activated cooling fans. The custom exhaust system is stainless steel with stainless Flowmaster mufflers.  The interior is custom and executed in leather and suede. Lizard skin ceramic insulating material is applied to the floors and interior roof. The seats are a 2 + 2 layout with full power front seats with a center console. The polished tilt steering column is from Air Ride Technologies and has dimmer controls. Billet Specialties provided the leather wrapped custom steering wheel. The polished, one-piece dash insert is from Pete’s Fabrications and is fitted with custom Classic Instruments. The heater and air conditioning unit are by Vintage Air; power windows with power wing windows and a Pioneer stereo system complete a welcoming environment.  The exterior finish is also custom and utilizes PPG materials. Additional eye-catching details are seen in a stainless steel grille, custom polished billet hood hinges, new Danchuk body badges, custom polished stainless trim elements, Advanced chrome plating, smoothie custom-fabricated one-piece front and rear bumpers, plus Boze Speedster wheels. This is a beautifully built and presented machine that has been stored and cared for in a climate-controlled environment.</car>
  <car id="_184561924" price="74800">This 1955 Nomad is finished in black over a red interior and is driven by a LT1 V-8 engine with a 4I60 transmission. The engine has an all street performance front drive and plenty of chrome engine accents are found under the hood. There is also a polished Griffin radiator with a custom chrome front support. Rack-and-pinion steering, four-wheel disc brakes, Billet Specialties wheels, BFGoodrich tires, all new chrome and stainless that is “show-quality” polished are all great features for this car, as is the louvered hood. The interior has Classic gauges, Pete and Jakes dash trim, Iditdit steering column with a custom wood wheel, hidden Sony Xplod system that features a subwoofer six-disc changer, amp and a matching Sony head unit. The car is a breathtaking beauty and has won numerous awards and was featured in a 2013 Street Rodder magazine.</car>
  <car id="_184562177" price="148500">The debate as to which of the classic mid-fifties Chevys is the best looking will go on forever. Some prefer the subtlety of the 1955, while others thrive on the flamboyance of the finned 1957 models; many enthusiasts opine the 1956 embodies the perfect balance of the other two.  The subtle changes to the Chevy’s body design in 1956 gave it a fresh, new, lighter appearance. Inside, the dash retained the dual cowl look, but now the mesh matched that of the front grille. Chevy also proved to the world that their full-size cars were not just rolling sculptures by setting new speed records and winning races.   This lovely Matador Red and Indian Ivory example features a deluxe red and white interior, and it has received a full and complete rotisserie restoration. This outstanding Chevy runs with a V-8 engine that has dual four-barrel carbs and “batwing” air cleaner assembly. The engine was prepared by Atlanta’s Tom Trainer, a recognized authority on this type of engine.  The car is generously equipped and includes a Powerglide transmission, Wonderbar radio, Continental kit, rare NOS rear antenna, windshield washer, wire-basket factory wheel covers, whitewall tires, dual mirrors, date-coded spiral shocks, front and rear accessory bumper guards, all-stainless steel exhaust system; power top, seat, windows, brakes and steering.  This exceptional offering has always been a trailered show car that resides in a climate-controlled setting. In February 2010 it won first place in the 1956 “Trailer Restored Senior Class” at the 18th Annual Chevy Classic Winter Nationals in Cocoa Beach, Florida, impressively scoring 991 points from a possible 1,000 total score.</car>
  <car id="_184562689" price="33950">Powered by a rebuilt 350-cid V-8 engine, this beautiful Biscayne was the recipient of a frame up restoration in 2008. The interior was completely redone by Brian Bohide. The candy red paint is beautiful and set off nicely by the all new chrome, stainless steel and five-spoke wheels. All of the glass was replaced as well. With multiple best paint awards at the Duck Tail run, this outstanding example is ready for you to enjoy and show.</car>
  <car id="_184562945" price="36850">This is an award-winning Chevy Apache that is vibrant in bright orange with an equally eye-catching orange and white interior that features bucket seats. The engine has been upgraded to a 350-cid V-8 GM crate engine that is mated to an automatic transmission. Along with power steering and power brakes, the Apache displays a finished oak bed floor, dual mirrors, chrome five-spoke wheels and low-profile blackwall tires.</car>
  <car id="_184562946" price="40700">This full custom Impala looks quite sporty in its blue finish with white pearl interior. The 348-cid V-8 engine is set up with three carburetors and mated to a four-speed manual transmission. The engine compartment is presented with a great deal of chrome components, stainless hose and Aeroquip fittings. The interior has a matching white custom headliner, striped acrylic control knobs, chrome dashboard, bucket seats, center console and modern white-faced instrumentation. The Impala rides low and has a louvered hood, lake pipes, chrome reverse wheels and whitewall tires.</car>
  <car id="_184563713" price="28200">Running a 350-cid V-8 engine and a turbo 350 automatic transmission, this Bel Air wagon is presented in light blue with a white roof that has been intentionally aged to show patina and give it a rat rod style. The Chevy has front and rear Air Ride Technologies suspension, dual exhaust, polished aluminum American Racing wheels, power steering and power brakes.</car>
  <car id="_184563714" price="66000">This is reported to be an absolutely tremendous “triple black” 1962 Corvette “fuelie” in regard to both its cosmetic and running condition. It is attractively presented in Tuxedo Black with a black convertible top and black vinyl interior. The heart of this machine is its impressive 327-cid, 360-hp V-8 fuel-injected powerplant and the corresponding four-speed manual transmission. The drivetrain is reported to be correct for this car, and it is stated that the Rochester fuel injection is in excellent working condition and that the Corvette starts and runs effortlessly.   Launched in 1956, it was the second series cars that earned Corvette the title of “America’s Sports Car.” The clean good looks of Harley Earl’s new body struck a chord with the American public, and the new design was soon outselling the older style, even at its peak, by a margin of three to one. The big news from Corvette in 1962, which represented the final year of the first-generation models with solid rear axles, was the enlarged 327-cubic inch V-8. This 15-percent increase in engine displacement brought with it a meaningful jump in both horsepower and torque, rendering the Corvette even easier and more fun to drive. The Corvette gained a competitive edge on the racetrack, and it was a winner on the sales floor as well, with 1962 sales fully one-third higher than 1961 levels.   Under Zora Arkus-Duntov, the Corvette team had plenty of high-performance parts on the shelf to support the growing number of racers, even as they worked feverishly on the upcoming Sting Ray. In 1962, the most-powerful Corvette engine was the regular production, order number 582, fuel-injected 327 V-8, now offered in just one very highly developed state of tune with a hot solid-lifter camshaft, free-breathing cylinder heads, and the proven Rochester mechanical fuel-injection unit. Amazingly, 1,918 Corvette buyers, representing 13-percent of total production, opted for this relatively expensive option in 1962, paying an additional $484.20 to enjoy the growing mystique and performance of the “fuelie.”</car>
  <car id="_184563715" price="151250">The Impala SS, with its 409-cid V-8, was the top of the musclecar order in 1962, but it was the purpose-built “lightweight” models with extensive aluminum upgrades that earned Chevrolet’s big-block its legendary status. Chevy introduced its W-series cast-iron engine family in 1958 as a next performance step beyond the popular 265-cid and 283-cid small-block V-8s. The first “W” was a 348-cid powerplant that could be mated to three two-barrel carburetors for a total output of 315 horsepower. On December 17, 1960, Chevy announced it was enlarging the engine to 409 cubic inches and would offer the new V-8 with its full-size 1961 Impala Super Sport (SS) model. Don Nicholson won the 1961 NHRA Winternationals in the Stock Eliminator class at Pomona, California behind the wheel of a 409-powered Impala SS, proving very quickly that Chevy’s new big-block was a superior piece of engineering. Twelve stock car victories that year added to the car’s reputation. Nicholson and a 409 Impala SS repeated their Winternationals Stock Eliminator victory in 1962, but Chevy kept developing speed parts for its big drag car. Unable to get more power from the 409, engineers focused on making the car lighter, which meant shaving pounds from every conceivable part. They replaced the sheetmetal hood, fenders, inner wheelwells, bumpers, brackets and other associated pieces with aluminum elements, trimming 120 pounds from a 3,500-pound automobile. Lightening the car’s front end helped transfer weight to the rear tires under acceleration, which reduced quarter-mile times. Only 18 Impala SSs received the aluminum components in 1962, including this unbelievable machine. Chevrolet built an exclusive number of lightweight Impalas for such clients as the aforementioned “Dyno” Don Nicholson, along with names such as Dave Strickler, Buddy Martin, Dick Harrell and John Zintsmaster, whose Kokomo, Indiana-based Zintsmaster Chevrolet, owned and ran the 1962 factory lightweight Impala that is being offered. This SS 409 was shipped to the Zintsmaster Chevrolet dealership in Kokomo, Indiana, and it survives with its documentation intact; some relating it’s all too brief racing career. The current owner reports that this is the only known surviving factory-documented car. The Zintsmaster car is commonly recognized as the most original, factory-built lightweight that the respected experts of the marque know about. This Impala SS was raced by the Zintsmaster Chevrolet dealership in essentially the very state that it is now being presented; a virtual time capsule. The lightweight Impala SS was driven by Dave Mason, whose name is still painted on the door. Zintsmaster took this car to the 1962 U.S. Nationals at Indianapolis Raceway Park where Mr. Mason ran it in the low 12-second range at 115-mph down the famed quarter-mile strip. Shortly after that, the car was described as being retired from competition and placed in private storage, where it then remained out of sight for over 20 years. It is said that Mr. Zintsmaster kept the lightweight SS 409 with its documentation until 1988 when it first was sold into another private collection. The rare Ermine White Impala lightweight racecar remains fundamentally unchanged since it raced at the Indy Nationals. It preserves almost all its original paint, except for slight touch-ups. A Roman Red stripe runs the length of both sides and the Zintsmaster Chevrolet is advertised as “Indiana’s Fastest Trader.” The original red bucket seat interior, the original whitewall tires from its last racing season, the original dual-quad 409-cid, 409-hp V-8 engine, and the original BorgWarner floor-mounted four-speed, plus the original 4.56:1 Posi-traction rear end are all part of this amazing platform. To add even more status, the engine was built by the legendary Bill Thomas, later of Cheetah fame. Today, the retired drag racer registers only 5,500 miles. The interior is a standard 1962 Impala SS layout with radio and heater delete, with a tachometer mounted on the dash. Color-keyed factory steel wheels are still with the car, as is the spare in the trunk and Zintsmaster Chevrolet sticker on the rear bumper. Along with the original window sticker, this important piece of automotive history is accompanied by numerous newspaper articles with race results. The Zintsmaster SS lightweight has also been featured in multiple magazine articles that further chronicles that it represents the best of the best, with its racing pedigree and originality intact and on display.</car>
  <car id="_184563969" price="189200">This beautiful Tuxedo Black Corvette is one of only 2,610 fitted with the 327-cid, 360-hp L84 fuel-injected V-8 engine; the most powerful engine option available. The engine also came from GM with a special cam and mechanical lifters. Coupled to a close-ratio four-speed manual transmission and Posi-traction rear end, this car was a dominate street racer in its day, accelerating from 0- to 60-mph in a mere 5.9-seconds. With a matching black interior, this Sting Ray also displays the desirable factory aluminum wheels with knock-off hubs, AM radio and whitewall tires.  In 1963 Chevrolet introduced the one-year-only Corvette split-window coupe designed by Larry Shinoda under the styling direction of Bill Mitchell. The design was inspired by Mitchell's 1959 Stingray racer and the 1961 Mako Shark concept car. In addition to the rear split-window design, the 1963 Corvette featured faux hood vents, a pointed hood bulge or “stinger,” and a raised spine across the roof. These design elements were eliminated in 1964, making the 1963 model rare and desirable among collectors.  The Corvette featured rear independent suspension designed by famed GM engineer Zora Arkus-Duntov. The Corvette also benefited from one of the greatest engines of all times, the 327-cid version of the Chevy “small-block.” Compact light and capable of staggering amounts of horsepower, it was also a relatively inexpensive engine. The 1963 Corvette was available in four engines options rated between 250- and 360-hp. Chevrolet built 21,513 Corvette Sting Rays in 1963. The production was a near-equal division between convertibles and split-window coupes.</car>
  <car id="_184564225" price="37400">Triple taillights tell us this is an Impala. Chevrolet wanted to be sure people knew you were driving the top-of-the-line, as lesser Chevies made do with dual taillights. The Impala name appeared for the first time in 1958 as a deluxe trim and appearance package on the Bel Air hardtop and convertible. It became a separate, top-of-the-line series in 1959.  Big news for Chevrolet in 1964 was the all-new mid-size Chevelle, but the full-size Chevrolet remained the sales leader with 1.6 million sold. After all, why mess with a good thing? As such, the big Chevy received minor changes with an update on the new-for-1963 body shell: a more rounded look with a flatter grille and redesigned rear panel.  The SS or Super Sport was considered a separate series for the first time rather than an Impala option package. In SS trim, this was one handsome car. The Impala quickly became the symbol for luxury and performance in the early sixties and introduced Chevrolet’s signature “SS” brand of performance.  A perfect example is this 409 Super Sport. It was definitely built with performance in mind with the 340 horsepower engine and a four-speed transmission. Features include bucket seats with center console, stainless tri-bar wheel covers, engine-turned trim on the rear cove molding, instrument panel and console; and discreet placement of SS badges on the exterior.  Other options include the column-mounted tachometer, power steering, AM radio, trunk light and, most notably, the very rare vinyl top. Of the nearly 100,000 Impalas built for 1964, only 7,326 had this option, according to records. The body and paint reflect quality of a fresh restoration, and only minor pitting is found on some window trim. Overall, it is a very clean and striking triple black Impala that is dressed to impress.</car>
  <car id="_184564737" price="42900">The 1966 Corvette carried over much of the prior years’ designs with a few subtle changes. A Corvette script was now found on the hood, while the roof vents, previously both functional and non-functional, were deleted completely. The base engine was bumped from 250 horsepower up to 300. This little red Corvette sports a matching leather interior. It is equipped with power steering, power disc brakes, AM/FM radio, power antenna, telescoping steering wheel, clock and spinner wheel covers. The small-block V-8 engine is mated to a four-speed transmission. It is noted that the folding top, possibly original to the car, fits very well, but has minor defects. With newer paint, the fit and finish of this roadster makes for a very nice driver that can be enjoyed without worry.</car>
  <car id="_184564738" price="27500">The Chevy II, born as economical car with either a four or six cylinder engine was first offered for the 1962 model year. As the Chevy II developed, horsepower ratings increased, and styling changes were made each year. In 1966 the Chevy II/Nova was restyled in keeping with the bigger Chevrolet designs and Super Sport trim as well as V-8 engines were readily available. Equipped with a 327 small-block and an automatic transmission, this silver SS looks ready for a street race with its five-spoke Weld wheels. This Nova is very clean in every area, from the detailed engine compartment to the neat-as-a pin bucket seat interior. Notable features include headers, four-barrel carburetor, console, aftermarket performance gauges and the original AM radio. This is a perfect entry level option for anyone wanting to experience an easy to drive and enjoy musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_184564993" price="250250">1967 was the year that was not meant to be, at least not for the Sting Ray as we know it. Chevrolet had hoped to launch a brand new body style for this model year but concern about the aerodynamic efficiency of the new design caused its postponement. As is so often the case, this production glitch enabled the Sting Ray to evolve and, in the process, offer one of the most awesome cars to hit the road. Some would argue it was the best Corvette ever. The bodywork was given only a few cosmetic changes since it was not expected to remain in production, but major developments took place beneath the hood. Although the two small-block engines remained, still rated at 300 and 350 horsepower, big-block 427 cubic inch engines were rated as high as 435 horsepower as seen here. Showing just 5,900 original miles from new, this 100-percent original and non-restored time capsule is among the lowest mileage examples of the 427/435 Sting Rays in existence. Purchased new by a GM engineer, it was stored in a climate controlled environment for 40 years. This exceptionally original survivor wears the original and desirable Marlboro Maroon paint, original black interior, original drivetrain and engine compartment, chrome and stainless. Also included is the original tank sticker, Protect-O-Plate and a well-documented ownership history. A true benchmark automobile, it’s impossible to duplicate options include L71 427-cid, 435-hp tri-power V-8, M21 close ratio four-speed transmission, Posi-traction axle, F41 special suspension, N11 off-road exhaust system, shoulder harness, transistor ignition, AM/FM radio and 775 x 15 redline tires. Having received multiple NCRS awards and Top Flight Status, this is an ultimate Blue-Chip Corvette that is worthy of the finest collection.</car>
  <car id="_184564994" price="137500">Having received a beautifully executed frame-off restoration, this handsome Corvette is not only finished in the popular Silver Pearl with black stinger and interior combination, it is driven by the desirable and fearsome 427-cid, 435-hp V-8 engine that has three two-barrel carbs and is mated to a four-speed manual transmission. The Corvette also has an AM radio, removable accessory hardtop, headrests, redline tires; power windows, brakes and steering.</car>
  <car id="_184565505" price="33000">Powered by a small-block V-8 engine that has performance accessories and is backed by an automatic transmission, this Camaro is finished in Rally Green with a black interior and has the RS and SS accessories, which includes the desirable hidden headlights. The car has bucket seats, console-shift, seatbelts, rear deck spoiler, back-up lights, front and rear bumper guards; pwer top, steering and disc brakes. The paint is absolutely beautiful and the soft-top is new. The Camaro also has the correct factory-style "hockey stick" accent stripes.</car>
  <car id="_184565506" price="77000">Chevrolet’s first-generation Camaro facelift would serve the 1969 model year only. While major mechanical components were carried over from 1968, new sheetmetal, except the hood and trunk lid, gave the car a substantially sportier look. New door skins, rear quarter panels and rear valance panel also gave the car a much lower, wider and aggressive look. The RS option comprised a special black-painted grille with concealed headlights and headlight washers, fender striping, simulated rear fender louvers, front and rear wheel opening moldings, black body sill and more. "This is our mean streak," is how Chevrolet described its new-for-1969 Z28 in selected advertisements. In addition to the model's standard Turbo-Fire V-8 engine, buyers received quick-ratio steering, special suspension, Rally stripes, Z28 emblems and more. Mandatory options included power disc brakes and manual transmission with Hurst floor-mounted shifter. A full concours-quality rotisserie restoration has brought this vintage Camaro to the finest quality any collector could hope to find. It is presented as a Z28 with RS features, which includes the desirable and visually appealing covered headlights. Originally finished in green, it now wears a stunning black finish with optional and functional cowl hood and both front and rear spoilers. The drivetrain is a 302-cid V-8 engine and a four-speed transmission as prescribed by the Z28 package. Under the hood, everything is in place, down to the factory smog equipment, Delco battery, factory-type markings, plus proper GM hoses and clamps. It is a power brakes, non-power steering version and also has a Delco AM/FM radio. Goodyear bias-ply wide tread GT tires are mounted on all four corners with Rally wheels, while the deluxe black interior features a center console and Rally Pack gauges. Only 140 miles have been driven since completion on this best-of-the-best Camaros.</car>
  <car id="_184565507" price="25300">Popular muscle cars tend to become scarce when swept up by enthusiasts and investors. Collectors turn to other means to create the car of their dreams, which is where tribute cars often come from. As seen in this example, tributes can be as nice, or nicer than the factory offered. Dolled up as a SS396, this Camaro is actually fitted with a 454 big block V-8, high-rise manifold, headers, and a 400 Turbo automatic transmission. Other notable equipment to be found is a transmission cooler, power steering, power disc brakes, five-spoke aluminum mag wheels with Cooper radial tires, cowl induction hood and chin spoiler. From the sparkling blue finish to the Hugger Orange engine, it is detailed and ready for the show or street. This is an excellent version of the very popular ’69 Camaro.</car>
  <car id="_184565508" price="62700">This sensational 1969 Chevrolet twin-turbo “Bomber Corvette” was built by S/S Motorsports of Sarasota exclusively for the 2008 SEMA show. The car utilizes an original 1969 Corvette as the “donor” and has a tube chassis, C5 Corvette front suspension, independent rear suspension, fully-adjustable coil-over shocks and six-piston street/track ventilated four-wheel disc braking system. The wheels are custom S/S (18x9 front and 18x12 rear) with street/track tires. The drivetrain includes a custom built 565-cid (9.0-liter), 1,200-hp Dart® S/S engine with twin turbochargers, fuel injection and runs on 93-octane pump fuel. It is further enhanced with Dart® Pro 1 aluminum heads, S/S polished aluminum valve covers, custom fabricated intake manifold and high-capacity aluminum radiator. The transmission is a paddle-shift 4L80E automatic with overdrive. Among the exterior features is custom paint with S/S stripe, custom four-inch side exhaust with fabricated ceramic-coated headers, L88 hood, 24-gallon fuel tank, pop-top fuel cap, plus T-tops and removable rear window. The interior is laden with special details that include a custom billet steering wheel with leather, paddle-shifters with digital display, high-capacity air conditioning system with multi-directional vents, carbon fiber dash with aircraft-style toggle and momentary switches, carbon fiber center console, full gauge package with S/S custom faces and bomber aircraft-type bezels, black leather racing seats with black suede inserts, pushbutton electric start, navigation system with in-dash monitor and a sound-deadening package.</car>
  <car id="_184565509" price="39600">Don Yenko was a Chevrolet dealer in Pennsylvania, with much interest in performance. A big-time Chevy racer, he earned four SCCA national titles including 1962 and 1963 and in 1965 formed Yenko Sports Cars. He worked with GM and in 1969, which agreed to give Yenko access to cars with factory-installed L72 engines through Central Office Production Orders. This was a way past GM internal red-tape whereby a 427-cid motor (forbidden in the Camaro) could be installed without upper-management approval. Today, true Yenko COPO Camaros demand prices well into the six-figure range, and clones or tribute cars, as offered here, are a more affordable way to enjoy the looks and blazing performance. With 6,190 miles after restoration, this 427 V-8, 425 horsepower coupe is an awesome machine. It also has a Hurst short shifter for the four-speed, dual exhaust, 12-bolt differential, power steering, power disc brakes, and 15-inch American Racing mags mounted with new BFGoodrich Radial T/A tires. The standard black interior features an AM radio, Sun Super Tach II tachometer, oil pressure and water temp gauges. The engine compartment is restored to appear correct as a Yenko down to the hoses and clamps. A cowl induction hood, rear and front chin spoilers complete this great looking musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_184565761" price="91300">This Chevelle SS LS5 convertible is the beneficiary of a full body-off restoration. The body is “laser-straight,” and the undercarriage is also completed with meticulous detail in mind. The car is impeccably completed as no expense was spared on the refurbishment. The powerful car is ready to drive, with plenty of go. The Chevelle was built in the GM plant in Baltimore, Maryland and runs with the desirable 454-cid, 360-hp V-8 LS5 engine that has a four-barrel carburetor and is mated to a Turbo-Hydramatic 400 automatic transmission. The exhaust is a dual system with 2.5-inch diameter pipes from front-to-rear. The Chevelle carries its correct drivetrain with matching numbers. Among the many features that are found on this car is factory air conditioning; uncommonly seen on convertibles of this era. Additionally there is a Cowl Induction hood, hood lock-pins, tinted glass, AM radio, performance suspension, bucket seats, center console, power convertible top and power brakes. SS wheels, dual center stripes and SS badging all contribute to the muscle aspect of this exciting car. Climate-controlled storage is another solid positive for this desirable machine.</car>
  <car id="_184570881" price="10175">The SS 454 pickup was a performance variant of the 1500-Series 1/2-ton truck produced by Chevrolet from 1990 through 1993. It was introduced to the public on September 1, 1989 and later inspired the production of its competitor, the Ford Lightning, in 1993. The SS 454 was a rather rare truck, as only 16,953 were produced in three years. Power is supplied by a “big-block” 454-cid V-8 producing 230-hp at 3,600-rpm and 385 foot-pounds of torque at 1,600-rpm. It is equipped with a three-speed automatic transmission and 3.73:1 rear axle ratio. Inside, bucket seats replaced the standard bench seat.  Nicely detailed underhood, this sinister black truck features a contrasting red cloth interior, power windows and door locks, AM/FM stereo radio, cassette tape deck, tilt steering wheel and integral bedliner.</car>
  <car id="_201339393" price="40150">The Chrysler 300B introduced for 1956 was similar to the previous year’s inaugural 300. It did, however, benefit from a revised tailfin treatment, as well as a new engine rated at 340 brake horsepower, a significant boost over the previous year’s offering of 300 brake horsepower. This second Chrysler 300 appeared around 12 months after the introduction of the C-300 and was again based on the New Yorker body with an Imperial grille, heavy-duty suspension and high performance hemi 354-cid V-8 engine. Styling and power refinements were seen, resulting in a modernized look, added muscle under the hood, plus a more civilized demeanor. The majority of the styling changes were shared with other Chrysler models and technical modifications centered on increased engine displacement, pushbutton automatic transmissions and the introduction of floating shoe, center-plane brakes. The impressive engine made the 300B the most powerful American car available.  Finished in Black with beige interior and black carpet, this 300B has been with the same owner for the last 35 years. It is reported by the current vendor to be the only similar car with factory air conditioning. While it is stated that the unit is complete, it is not currently in working order. The detailed engine compartment reflects a great deal of originality, plus the Chrysler runs and drives “as it should.” The interior has had reproduction seat covers added, but this was executed prior to the1990 purchase by the current vendor. The 300B has a replacement headliner from Gary Goers. Along with exceptional brightwork detail; additional equipment found on this uncommon beauty includes a two-speed PowerFlite automatic transmission, AM radio, a heater and power windows. This 300B rides on standard steel wheels shod with whitewall tires and checkered-style factory full wheel covers. Only 1,102 similar cars were produced in the 1956 model year.</car>
  <car id="_218123265" price="29700">The DeLorean DMC-12 sports car was the dream of John DeLorean, former General Manager of the Pontiac Division of General Motors. The car was built for the American market in 1981-1982 featuring novel gullwing doors with a fiberglass "underbody" to which non-structural brushed stainless steel panels were affixed. The car became iconic for its appearance in the movie Back to the Future as a modified time machine as well as for the trials and tribulations of founder John DeLorean. The prototype appeared in October 1976 and production began in 1981 in Northern Ireland with the first DMC-12 rolling off the production line on January 21.  Approximately 9,000 DMC-12s were made before production halted in early 1983.This five-speed DeLorean with power windows, power seats, cassette tape player and air conditioning has just 6,256 miles and is noted to be in great condition.</car>
  <car id="_234894337" price="88000">The Devin Special is a serious sports car. It has a tube frame, lightweight fiberglass body, aluminum interior, complete instrumentation, individual windscreens, functional hoodscoop, aluminum headrest, “eggcrate” grille, quick-fill fuel cap and sport mirrors. The Devin is finished in white and blue which represented American racing colors of the period; such as seen on the respected Cunningham team.  This exciting open cockpit two-seater was produced by Devin Enterprises in El Monte, California. This particular car is powered by a Chevrolet 283-cid V-8 engines with dual Carter AFB carburetors with an original Bill Devin dual four-barrel aluminum intake that Mr. Devin designed and cast himself. The owner reports that only around 15 of these components are known to exist. This unit is hooked up to a Muncie aluminum four-speed manual transmission and a Ford nine-inch rear end. The transmission has a Hurst shifter that is also stated to be “super rare.” The current owner contacted Hurst about the shifter, and sent them a photograph, as he had never seen a similar one. The Hurst people, he conveys, immediately attempted to buy the shifter as it was described to him as one of approximately 100 produced by Hurst in the 1960s. Despite a very generous offer, it remains with the Devin.  The exhaust is routed through large side pipes. Equipped with Ansen PIN drive wheels and correct Vintage Dunlop racing tires as it was in 1958. The chassis is set up with adjustable coil-over shocks up front and dual shock absorbers on both rear corners. The front brakes are discs and the rear has drums. This historically important car has only about 200 miles on a complete "period correct" professional restoration. The prior owner told the current vendor that the Devin was rescued from a barn in California.   The 1950s produced a unique time in American sports car racing. The ever-growing popularity of road racing in Southern California soon attracted independent car builders who embodied the inventive spirit and skill of the hot rod culture. Homemade specials began to challenge, and on occasion, beat the Ferraris, Jaguars and Maseratis.  Bill Devin was part of that scene, and out of this setting he created the Devin Special. Devin also manufactured fiberglass bodies to fit a wide variety of chassis’, giving talented hobbyists the opportunity to build their own sports car at a fraction of the cost.</car>
  <car id="_251671041" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_251674369" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_251674625" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_251676673" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_285214209" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_302008833" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_318784257" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_318788353" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_318791425" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335550465" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335551233" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335551234" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335552001" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335552257" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335552513" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335556097" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335556865" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335559681" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335559937" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335560449" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335560705" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335560706" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_335560961" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_352335873" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_369106177" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_385892097" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_385892098" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_402665473" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_419452161" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_436221441" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_452997121" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_469776385" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_469779457" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_486547713" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503331841" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503332353" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503332609" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503332610" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503332865" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_503332866" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_520104961" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_520109825" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_520110081" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_536891649" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_553650177" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_570440449" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587217153" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587217665" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587218177" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587218178" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587218433" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587218434" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587218945" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_587229697" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_603991809" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_620764673" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_637543681" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
</aoCars>
