<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE aoCars [
<!ELEMENT aoCars (car)*>
<!ELEMENT car ANY>
<!ATTLIST car id ID #REQUIRED>
<!ATTLIST car price CDATA #REQUIRED>
]>
<aoCars>
  <car id="_16798977" price="35200">In 1984 Honda commissioned Pininfarina to design the HP-X (Honda Pininfarina Experimental) featuring a 2.0-litre mid-mounted engine which later evolved into the production NSX. The Honda NSX was sold under the Acura brand name in North America and Hong Kong markets. The exotic was produced between 1990 and 2005 and is equipped with a mid-engine, all-aluminum V-6 featuring Honda&#x2019;s variable valve timing and electronic lift control called VTEC. Other notable features include an independent four-channel anti-lock brake system, titanium connecting rods to permit high engine rpm operation, and electric power steering. It was the first production car to use an all-aluminum monocoque body incorporating a revolutionary extruded aluminum alloy frame and suspension. This hot collectible is one of just 18,685 sold worldwide over 16 years of production and one of 1,093 red/black interior five-speed equipped 1991 models produced. It is fitted with Momo alloy wheels and an aftermarket CD changer.</car>
  <car id="_33570817" price="44550">This is an award winning AMX that features a nut-and-bolt restoration that utilizes many N.O.S. parts. Among the new old stock parts are rocker moldings, deck lid, rear valance, front fenders, grille, hood molding, headlight bezels, parking lights/turn signal lenses and housings, all side marker lamps, door latches and strikers, door seals, jamb bumpers, trunk seal, outer door handles with correct finish, gas tank, bolts and sending unit, along with many other components and trim details. &#xA0;This is a very well-equipped example that is finished in Bayshore Blue with a black interior; among the features are tilt steering wheel, center armrest and cushion (&#x201C;buddy seat&#x201D;), AM/FM radio, Light Group, Visibility Group, optional 15-inch Machine wheels, tinted glass, air conditioning, front spoiler, black rally stripes, black vinyl bucket seats, Go Package, space-saver spare, dual mirrors with driver&#x2019;s side remote; power steering and brakes. The engine is a 390-cid, 325-hp V-8 that is mated to a four-speed manual transmission. &#xA0;This fine AMX has placed first at the Hoosier Auto Show in Indianapolis in both 2003 and 2004. A first place was also won by this AMC at a Cincinnati concours d&#x2019;elegance in 2005. It has also won the First Junior Award at the AACA spring meet, and that fall, it won the AACA Senior Award at the prestigious and largely attended Hershey meet. In 2012 it won the AACA Grand National Award in Tennessee. As recently as 2013, it obtained the AACA top honor by winning the Senior Grand National Award in Moline, Illinois. &#xA0; The vendor does state that the original 360-cid engine was replaced with this correct, rebuilt 390-cid version that was optional to the car in 1970. The Bayshore Blue paint is also original spec for this 1970 model; it has been applied to replace the original Glen Green.</car>
  <car id="_50331649" price="126500">"The 1906 American Tourist was the first production automobile designed by Harry C. Stutz. Its Stutz-designed side-valve four-cylinder 336 cubic inch engine broke no new ground, but equally showed Stutz's appreciation for the desirable attributes of touring car engines, in this case a practical operating range of 125- to 1,450-rpm. Live axle suspension with semi-elliptical leaf springs and platform rear suspension with a semi-elliptical cross spring were characteristic of the highest quality automobiles of the day. Harry Stutz's Tourist showed its value, quality and practicality by earning its place in the American model lineup from its inception in 1906 until 1913, just a year before American ceased production in 1914. The Stutz-designed four-cylinder engine powered all automobiles built by American Motor Cars until 1913. American built some 45,000 automobiles in just 9 years, double the production of Packards in the same period. This 1906 American Tourist Roi des Belges Touring was restored years ago for one of the founders of car collecting in America, Dr. Samuel Scher. It is one of very few surviving examples of its model, a nearly unique example of an important milestone in both the evolution of the American automobile and in the development of Harry Stutz's experience and his concepts of automobile design. Finished in red with black mudguards, it has red leather upholstery and a black cloth top. The American eagle mascot spreads its wings proudly on the radiator cap. There are Rushmore acetylene headlights, Gray &amp; Davis kerosene sidelights, a magnificent Rushmore swivel-mounted acetylene searchlight on the cowl, Stewart speedometer and a brass bulb horn. The thoroughness of its restoration and the care it's had in the last two generations are reflected in the set of side curtains that still accompany it. One of the great automobiles of early American history, it will still show its heels to traffic with style and panache that is almost unknown today."</car>
  <car id="_67124481" price="47300">It&#x2019;s a car. It&#x2019;s a boat. Actually, it&#x2019;s both. Nothing draws a crowd like an Amphicar. Developed in West Germany, the Amphicar was aimed squarely at America&#x2019;s leisure market and debuted at the 1961 New York Auto Show. As the culmination of a 15-year, $25 million development program, the Amphicar was conceived by amphibious-vehicle pioneer Hans Trippel. A curious fusion of road-going and aquatic transport, it remains particularly popular as a unique and eye-catching collector&#x2019;s item with its amphibious design and twin-screw propellers. Powered by a 1,147-cc Triumph Herald inline four-cylinder engine mated to a four-speed manual transmission, it directed power to the rear wheels on land and, once on water, to twin propellers at the rear. This Amphicar is finished in Beach White and features a black soft-top, red steel wheels and chrome hubcaps, whitewall tires, red and white two-tone upholstery. Amphicar marketing highlighted the vehicle&#x2019;s ease of operation, and its unofficial &#x201C;770&#x201D; designation referred to its factory-claimed top speeds of seven knots on water and 70-mph on land. It is generally agreed that 3,878 were built through 1967, with the majority exported to the USA, far fewer are thought to remain.</car>
  <car id="_83910657" price="52250">The Aston Martin DB7 was launched in March 1993 at the Geneva Motor Show and marked the return of the six-cylinder Aston Martin. Penned by Ian Callum, the rakish lines of the DB7 were beautiful, hearkening back to iconic models from the sixties. Although it was originally intended to be an "entry level" Aston Martin, it quickly evolved into much more. &#xA0;In 1999 Aston Martin squeezed its first production 12-cylinder engine into the DB7 to create the potent DB7 Vantage. The Aston Martin DB7 is a Grand Touring car in the finest tradition. Produced from 1994 to 2004, the DB7 proved to be one of the most popular Aston Martin models. &#xA0;For those seeking employment as an international spy, there is really only one marque of automobile for daily transportation needs, the heralded name of Aston Martin. This DB7 nicely fits the bill with a well-trimmed black leather interior that is fully loaded with all of the accouterment required for sports car motoring. Aside from very light wear to the driver-side seat bolster and a high-end Alpine entertainment system, this low-mile Vantage appears like new from the inside. On the Titanium Silver exterior, no obvious blemishes are to be found on the soft folding top or the paint and trim. It is fitted with 19-inch alloy rims wrapped with Yokohama rubber. The 5.9-liter, 420 horsepower V-12 and five-speed transmission with steering shift will ensure great performance on the next mission.</car>
  <car id="_100670977" price="145750">The beautiful supercharged 852 Phaeton Sedan offered here has been driven and enjoyed by its owner, an enthusiastic Auburn, Indiana resident, on several regional ACD Club tours. Reliability has been excellent, and the car runs beautifully and performs well at highway speeds, with the optional &#x201C;Dual Ratio&#x201D; rear axle functioning properly, as confirmed by recent road testing by an Auctions America specialist. No less beautiful cosmetically, it is in &#x201C;high-end driver&#x201D; condition, with excellent chrome, interior, and top, and only slight age showing to the rich green paint.&#xA0; &#xA0;The tan leather interior is an attractive complement to the body tone and features elegant instrumentation with a damascene-type dashboard. The exterior exhaust pipes and optional sidemounted spare with cover add sportiness and style. Chrome headlights and factory installed trunk were both optional equipment in 1935. The trunk adds 13.5-cubic feet of luggage space. Wire wheels, whitewall tires, dual mirrors, chrome taillights and vacuum windshield wipers are all part of this desirable platform. It will continue to be an outstanding tour car and welcome at ACD Club events. The Auburn has been certified by the Auburn-Cord-Duesenberg Club as a Category No. 1, Certified Original Car. It is also one of the most drivable and enjoyable of all Full Classics, as recognized by the CCCA. &#xA0;Introduced in 1935, the all-new 851 featured beautiful Gordon Buehrig-penned styling and offered an optional Switzer-Cummins centrifugal supercharger, which boosted output by 30 percent to 150-hp. Developed by Kurt Beier at Schwitzer-Cummins and adapted to the Auburn-Lycoming inline eight-cylinder engine by Augie Duesenberg and Pearl Watson, the supercharger ran at six times engine speed and generated useful boost from 2,000-rpm upwards. &#xA0; The Auburn 852 was the last hurrah for the Auburn Automobile Company. As was the case with many of the independent manufacturers, their final products were often among their best. The styling, introduced in 1935, was the last Gordon Buehrig designed Auburn line to see production. &#xA0; Established in 1903, the Auburn Automobile Company matured into a well-respected builder of reliable cars, but it was not until E.L. Cord assumed the company&#x2019;s presidency in 1924 that its market stature grew. In fact, as the once-buoyant auto market collapsed following Black Tuesday, Auburn&#x2019;s sales continued to increase. By 1931, Auburn was the 13th largest American automaker, but the triumph was short-lived, as sales fell drastically in 1932 and 1933.</car>
  <car id="_117464577" price="64900">In March 1995 at the Geneva Motor Show, Rolls-Royce Motors unveiled its convertible version of the Continental R, the Bentley Azure. Now considered a modern classic, the Pininfarina-designed Azure is acknowledged by Rolls-Royce and Bentley enthusiasts to be one of the most desirable cars ever built. The two-door open tourer seats four adults in sumptuous comfort, thanks in part to its brilliant computer-controlled automatic ride control. Whether enjoying a leisurely top-down Sunday drive or covering great distances at speed and experiencing the thrill of putting the car through its paces, the well-mannered Azure is the definitive driver&#x2019;s car. This 2000 Azure convertible has covered only 26,000 miles from new and is beautifully presented in rich black body color; accented with matching red-piped black leather upholstery and a black cloth top. It has Bentley embroidered headrests, tinted glass, and two matching Bentley umbrellas in the trunk, as well as all the standard luxury conveniences expected of a Bentley. It is in exceptionally clean and well maintained condition consistent with the low recorded mileage. Boosted by a Garrett turbocharger the big 6.75-liter V-8 delivers 400 brake horsepower and 590-lb/ft of torque. The limited production Azure convertible was as dominant on the road as its luxury and exclusivity dominated the boulevards of resorts and spas. Priced in excess of $300,000 when new, it is an automobile to be proud to own and drive. Only 1,308 units were built until production ended in 2003. In that time, just 709 Azures were exported to the U.S. market.</car>
  <car id="_134230529" price="42900">When BMW undertook the manufacturing of Renzo Rivolta&#x2019;s Isetta in 1955, the firm incorporated some changes. The drivetrain was redesigned to use their 247 cubic centimeter four-cycle motorcycle engine. The gearbox output was coupled to a shaft through a rubber universal joint, which led, through another rubber joint, to the chain case. Inside were double drive chains running in oil to the solid rear axle. This arrangement made the whole power unit much quieter and reduced vibration. In fact, so much of the car was re-engineered that no earlier Iso parts were used, nor were they interchangeable. The front suspension was also reconfigured to a swing arm arrangement. Changes to the body included raising the headlights above the fenders so that they attached directly to the body. As with this car, in 1956 the engine displacement was increased to 297 cubic centimeters and compression was raised to achieve 13 horsepower. Although top speed did not increase from 53-mph, there was a marked increase in much-welcome torque, which helped on hills. More than 161,000 Isettas were built through 1962, along with some 34,000 BMW 600s, an elongated, four-passenger version with a flat-twin engine and a conventional rear axle. This rare example of a surviving European bubble window Isetta has the highly desirable &#x201C;Z mold trim&#x201D; and two-tone paint. It is the recipient of an excellent restoration and is very attractive in red and white; it has primarily red tartan upholstery and a black fabric sunroof. Very well detailed with front vent windows, dual mirrors, luggage rack and whitewall tires, it is an excellent example of the popular European microcar.</car>
  <car id="_134242049" price="98450">The Z8 is BMW&#x2019;s spiritual successor to the 1950s 507 roadster. Both cars use a long hood with short deck design to create a powerful and sporty appearance. This limited production roadster with optional hardtop is equipped with a 4.9-liter DOHC V-8 as used in the M5, mated to a proper six-speed manual gearbox and producing nearly 400-hp. The Z8 has electronic traction control and four-wheel ventilated disc brakes with ABS and factory alloy wheels. This example has less than 51,000 miles and is handsomely presented in Titanium Silver Metallic with a black leather interior. The removable hardtop is in the same color as the body and has a rear window defogger. The soft-top is black and the remote mirrors are chrome. Luxury appointments are also prominent; these include alloy and leather interior trim elements, air conditioning, AM/FM/CD, Xenon lighting, fixed hoop rollover protection; power seats, door locks, windows, steering and brakes.&#xA0; In developing the Z8, BMW married form and function like never before. The design is flawless from any angle, inside and out, carried over from Henrik Fisker&#x2019;s Z07 concept introduced at Tokyo in 1997 and paying homage to the Count Albrecht Goertz-designed 507 of the 1950s with side vents, a sleek front end and such retro touches as a banjo-type steering wheel. &#xA0;With 50/50 weight distribution and the acceleration of a Ferrari 360 Modena, this was BMW&#x2019;s fastest roadster to date, the movie car choice of James Bond and a true supercar with brilliant braking and cornering. Motor Trend magazine brought out its true &#x201C;M&#x201D; potential, achieving a 0- to 60-mph sprint of just 4.2 seconds, and top speed was reported as 155-mph.</car>
  <car id="_151005953" price="56100">In 1949, this was Buick&#x2019;s glamorous way to go places &#x2013; with its top up or down it was one of the sharpest cars on any boulevard. Motoring thrills are gathered by its behavior on the road, wide seating and ease of having standard equipment such as the automatically-operated top, front seat and windows. This wonderful car has been restored from top-to-bottom starting with a solid, rust-free southern car that was one family owned for 50 years. The restoration process utilized mainly N.O.S. parts. The car has received new paint, interior, top, chrome, wiring and mechanicals; including new brakes, engine rebuild, transmission rebuild &#x2013; even the factory radio has been refurbished and is in perfect working condition. The Sequoia Cream finish is handsomely matched with a low-profile black soft-top that has red piping, and the interior is upholstered in red vinyl. The engine is a factory original Fireball 248-cid, 115-hp straight eight-cylinder and the transmission is automatic. Among the features found on the Buick are &#x201C;VentiPorts,&#x201D; AM radio, clock, backup lights, fender skirts, bumper guards with accessory bar, distinguishing brightwork, red steel wheels with factory wheel covers and wide whitewall tires. This is a quite uncommon and sought-after Buick that has an iconic status and is presented in a meticulous fashion.</car>
  <car id="_151011841" price="13200">First introduced as a personal luxury car, Buick took their Riviera, offered bigger engine displacement, and the &#x201C;Gentleman&#x2019;s Musclecar&#x201D; was born. Over 1.1 million Riveras were produced from 1963 to 1999, and perhaps the most memorable versions were the early seventies&#x2019; boattail styles seen from 1971-1973. Seen here, this two-tone green Riviera has the big 455 cubic inch engine topped with a four-barrel carburetor. The engine compartment is loaded with goodies such as power steering and brakes, as well as air conditioning. The interior is in remarkably well-preserved condition with medium green cloth fabrics and matching door panels and dash. The odometer shows 30,462 miles; perhaps giving reason for the fine original quality throughout. It also features cruise control, power windows and power seat. This is a prime example of Buick&#x2019;s successful, powerful and memorable boattail Riviera.</car>
  <car id="_151015681" price="16500">Buick&#x2019;s Grand National was menacing right out of the box. Most were black, with blackout trim. The interior was finished in a plethora of gray tones and fabrics, and the instrumentation included a tach and a boost gauge. Naturally, the suspension got stiffer springs and anti-roll bars, plus Goodyear radials on special aluminum wheels. Buick continued development on the GN package, and soon came an intercooler, along with 235 horsepower for 1986, then 245 horses in &#x2019;87. This black Buick shows only 40,000 miles from new and still wears its original paint. The two-tone cloth interior is in excellent condition and features an automatic transmission, power locks and windows, air conditioning, AM/FM/cassette and tilt wheel. The 3.8 turbo V-6 engine compartment is also detailed to appear as new.</car>
  <car id="_167784961" price="73700">Named Biarritz, the 1956 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible carried a substantial factory price tag of $6,501 when new. With only 2,150 examples built, this Biarritz is truly a masterpiece of Cadillac craftsmanship. It is difficult to find a better example of GM's styling and engineering prowess than viewing the 1956 Cadillac Eldorado. Surviving examples remain highly sought-after today and they continue to rank among the most luxurious and elegant automobiles ever to come from GM during the fabulous 1950s. For the first time, the Eldorado also had a hardtop model that was named the Seville. &#xA0;This Eldorado is finished in Black with a black convertible top and a classly black and white two-tone interior. It is equipped with gold-finished Saber-Spoke wheels, wide whitewall tires, radio, clock; power top, seat, windows, steering and brakes, plus all the other inherent Eldorado features for 1956. The 1956 Cadillac is powered by a twin-carb 365-cid V-8 engine with 305-hp and is connected to a Hydra-Matic automatic transmission. This power equipment was standard in period for this model.</car>
  <car id="_167785217" price="181500">In 1957 Dwight Eisenhower was in the White House, Sputnik orbited planet Earth and Elvis Presley appeared on the Ed Sullivan show for the third and what would be last time. Presley also owned a new 1957 Cadillac Eldorado Biarritz, the car that marked the pinnacle of automotive ownership for many Americans. At over $7,000, it was achievable for the individual who had attained personal success. Someone like Elvis, climbing their way up the ladder and had the desire to reward themselves with the best that money could buy. It spoke to that success with vast amounts of chrome, impressive highway-devouring performance, and styling that only Harley Earl's studio could have dreamt up.</car>
  <car id="_184561665" price="28200">Running a 350-cid V-8 engine and a turbo 350 automatic transmission, this Bel Air wagon is presented in light blue with a white roof that has been intentionally aged to show patina and give it a rat rod style. The Chevy has front and rear Air Ride Technologies suspension, dual exhaust, polished aluminum American Racing wheels, power steering and power brakes.</car>
  <car id="_184561921" price="48400">While this Chevy truck displays many original attributes, it has been refurbished by A-Car Restorations of Reedsville, Wisconsin using a 350-cid V-8 General Motors crate engine that is matched to a floor-shift five-speed manual transmission. The rear end is a nine-inch Ford unit. The truck is very nicely presented in Viper Red and has a tan interior with a black tonneau cover. The steel wheels are color-keyed and have been mounted with wide whitewalls and are fit with chrome hubcaps and trim rings. Heidts front suspension, stainless steel exhaust, stereo; power steering and brakes are other features on this fine looking 1955 3100 truck.</car>
  <car id="_184561922" price="57200">The Tri-Five years from Chevrolet have always been favored 1950s American classics. This 1955 Bel Air is shown in Skyline Blue with India Ivory and beautiful two-tone slate blue upholstery. The interior is very well-restored with great attention to fit and finish of each component. It is powered by a 265 V-8 with a three-speed manual overdrive transmission. The engine bay is highlighted with chrome valve covers and has been detailed to better than factory standards. The underside of the chassis is equally detailed and impressive. Four new Coker wide whitewall radials have been mounted onto the correct steel wheels. The car also has full wheel covers, fender skirts, dual exhaust, dual external mirrors, tinted windshield, power top, original radio and clock, plus front and rear bumper guards. This is a prime opportunity to forego the time and cost of a restoration and to simply purchase a fully restored Bel Air.</car>
  <car id="_184561923" price="101200">This custom Bel Air has received a total frame-off restoration that includes extensive new sheetmetal. The chassis is from Custom Progressive and is powder-coated in blue that matches the body color. It is powered by a fuel-injected GM LS2 6.0-liter V-8 that is dyno&#x2019;d at 507 horsepower at the rear wheels. Along with a custom cam, the engine has a Magnuson supercharger with 40-pound injectors and custom intercooler with a remote custom tank. The transmission is a T-56 six-speed manual that has a hydraulic clutch system. Other mechanical workings consist of C4 Corvette front suspension components and narrowed Dana 44 rear end, also from a C4. The power brakes are hydraulic and by Hydratech with 12-inch Wilwood brake rotors and four-piston calipers. The custom radiator has custom computer-activated cooling fans. The custom exhaust system is stainless steel with stainless Flowmaster mufflers. &#xA0;The interior is custom and executed in leather and suede. Lizard skin ceramic insulating material is applied to the floors and interior roof. The seats are a 2 + 2 layout with full power front seats with a center console. The polished tilt steering column is from Air Ride Technologies and has dimmer controls. Billet Specialties provided the leather wrapped custom steering wheel. The polished, one-piece dash insert is from Pete&#x2019;s Fabrications and is fitted with custom Classic Instruments. The heater and air conditioning unit are by Vintage Air; power windows with power wing windows and a Pioneer stereo system complete a welcoming environment. &#xA0;The exterior finish is also custom and utilizes PPG materials. Additional eye-catching details are seen in a stainless steel grille, custom polished billet hood hinges, new Danchuk body badges, custom polished stainless trim elements, Advanced chrome plating, smoothie custom-fabricated one-piece front and rear bumpers, plus Boze Speedster wheels. This is a beautifully built and presented machine that has been stored and cared for in a climate-controlled environment.</car>
  <car id="_184561924" price="74800">This 1955 Nomad is finished in black over a red interior and is driven by a LT1 V-8 engine with a 4I60 transmission. The engine has an all street performance front drive and plenty of chrome engine accents are found under the hood. There is also a polished Griffin radiator with a custom chrome front support. Rack-and-pinion steering, four-wheel disc brakes, Billet Specialties wheels, BFGoodrich tires, all new chrome and stainless that is &#x201C;show-quality&#x201D; polished are all great features for this car, as is the louvered hood. The interior has Classic gauges, Pete and Jakes dash trim, Iditdit steering column with a custom wood wheel, hidden Sony Xplod system that features a subwoofer six-disc changer, amp and a matching Sony head unit. The car is a breathtaking beauty and has won numerous awards and was featured in a 2013 Street Rodder magazine.</car>
  <car id="_184562177" price="148500">The debate as to which of the classic mid-fifties Chevys is the best looking will go on forever. Some prefer the subtlety of the 1955, while others thrive on the flamboyance of the finned 1957 models; many enthusiasts opine the 1956 embodies the perfect balance of the other two. &#xA0;The subtle changes to the Chevy&#x2019;s body design in 1956 gave it a fresh, new, lighter appearance. Inside, the dash retained the dual cowl look, but now the mesh matched that of the front grille. Chevy also proved to the world that their full-size cars were not just rolling sculptures by setting new speed records and winning races. &#xA0; This lovely Matador Red and Indian Ivory example features a deluxe red and white interior, and it has received a full and complete rotisserie restoration. This outstanding Chevy runs with a V-8 engine that has dual four-barrel carbs and &#x201C;batwing&#x201D; air cleaner assembly. The engine was prepared by Atlanta&#x2019;s Tom Trainer, a recognized authority on this type of engine. &#xA0;The car is generously equipped and includes a Powerglide transmission, Wonderbar radio, Continental kit, rare NOS rear antenna, windshield washer, wire-basket factory wheel covers, whitewall tires, dual mirrors, date-coded spiral shocks, front and rear accessory bumper guards, all-stainless steel exhaust system; power top, seat, windows, brakes and steering. &#xA0;This exceptional offering has always been a trailered show car that resides in a climate-controlled setting. In February 2010 it won first place in the 1956 &#x201C;Trailer Restored Senior Class&#x201D; at the 18th Annual Chevy Classic Winter Nationals in Cocoa Beach, Florida, impressively scoring 991 points from a possible 1,000 total score.</car>
  <car id="_184562689" price="33950">Powered by a rebuilt 350-cid V-8 engine, this beautiful Biscayne was the recipient of a frame up restoration in 2008. The interior was completely redone by Brian Bohide. The candy red paint is beautiful and set off nicely by the all new chrome, stainless steel and five-spoke wheels. All of the glass was replaced as well. With multiple best paint awards at the Duck Tail run, this outstanding example is ready for you to enjoy and show.</car>
  <car id="_184562945" price="36850">This is an award-winning Chevy Apache that is vibrant in bright orange with an equally eye-catching orange and white interior that features bucket seats. The engine has been upgraded to a 350-cid V-8 GM crate engine that is mated to an automatic transmission. Along with power steering and power brakes, the Apache displays a finished oak bed floor, dual mirrors, chrome five-spoke wheels and low-profile blackwall tires.</car>
  <car id="_184562946" price="40700">This full custom Impala looks quite sporty in its blue finish with white pearl interior. The 348-cid V-8 engine is set up with three carburetors and mated to a four-speed manual transmission. The engine compartment is presented with a great deal of chrome components, stainless hose and Aeroquip fittings. The interior has a matching white custom headliner, striped acrylic control knobs, chrome dashboard, bucket seats, center console and modern white-faced instrumentation. The Impala rides low and has a louvered hood, lake pipes, chrome reverse wheels and whitewall tires.</car>
  <car id="_184563713" price="28200">Running a 350-cid V-8 engine and a turbo 350 automatic transmission, this Bel Air wagon is presented in light blue with a white roof that has been intentionally aged to show patina and give it a rat rod style. The Chevy has front and rear Air Ride Technologies suspension, dual exhaust, polished aluminum American Racing wheels, power steering and power brakes.</car>
  <car id="_184563714" price="66000">This is reported to be an absolutely tremendous &#x201C;triple black&#x201D; 1962 Corvette &#x201C;fuelie&#x201D; in regard to both its cosmetic and running condition. It is attractively presented in Tuxedo Black with a black convertible top and black vinyl interior. The heart of this machine is its impressive 327-cid, 360-hp V-8 fuel-injected powerplant and the corresponding four-speed manual transmission. The drivetrain is reported to be correct for this car, and it is stated that the Rochester fuel injection is in excellent working condition and that the Corvette starts and runs effortlessly.&#xA0; &#xA0;Launched in 1956, it was the second series cars that earned Corvette the title of &#x201C;America&#x2019;s Sports Car.&#x201D; The clean good looks of Harley Earl&#x2019;s new body struck a chord with the American public, and the new design was soon outselling the older style, even at its peak, by a margin of three to one. The big news from Corvette in 1962, which represented the final year of the first-generation models with solid rear axles, was the enlarged 327-cubic inch V-8. This 15-percent increase in engine displacement brought with it a meaningful jump in both horsepower and torque, rendering the Corvette even easier and more fun to drive. The Corvette gained a competitive edge on the racetrack, and it was a winner on the sales floor as well, with 1962 sales fully one-third higher than 1961 levels. &#xA0; Under Zora Arkus-Duntov, the Corvette team had plenty of high-performance parts on the shelf to support the growing number of racers, even as they worked feverishly on the upcoming Sting Ray. In 1962, the most-powerful Corvette engine was the regular production, order number 582, fuel-injected 327 V-8, now offered in just one very highly developed state of tune with a hot solid-lifter camshaft, free-breathing cylinder heads, and the proven Rochester mechanical fuel-injection unit. Amazingly, 1,918 Corvette buyers, representing 13-percent of total production, opted for this relatively expensive option in 1962, paying an additional $484.20 to enjoy the growing mystique and performance of the &#x201C;fuelie.&#x201D;</car>
  <car id="_184563715" price="151250">The Impala SS, with its 409-cid V-8, was the top of the musclecar order in 1962, but it was the purpose-built &#x201C;lightweight&#x201D; models with extensive aluminum upgrades that earned Chevrolet&#x2019;s big-block its legendary status. Chevy introduced its W-series cast-iron engine family in 1958 as a next performance step beyond the popular 265-cid and 283-cid small-block V-8s. The first &#x201C;W&#x201D; was a 348-cid powerplant that could be mated to three two-barrel carburetors for a total output of 315 horsepower. On December 17, 1960, Chevy announced it was enlarging the engine to 409 cubic inches and would offer the new V-8 with its full-size 1961 Impala Super Sport (SS) model. Don Nicholson won the 1961 NHRA Winternationals in the Stock Eliminator class at Pomona, California behind the wheel of a 409-powered Impala SS, proving very quickly that Chevy&#x2019;s new big-block was a superior piece of engineering. Twelve stock car victories that year added to the car&#x2019;s reputation. Nicholson and a 409 Impala SS repeated their Winternationals Stock Eliminator victory in 1962, but Chevy kept developing speed parts for its big drag car. Unable to get more power from the 409, engineers focused on making the car lighter, which meant shaving pounds from every conceivable part. They replaced the sheetmetal hood, fenders, inner wheelwells, bumpers, brackets and other associated pieces with aluminum elements, trimming 120 pounds from a 3,500-pound automobile. Lightening the car&#x2019;s front end helped transfer weight to the rear tires under acceleration, which reduced quarter-mile times. Only 18 Impala SSs received the aluminum components in 1962, including this unbelievable machine. Chevrolet built an exclusive number of lightweight Impalas for such clients as the aforementioned &#x201C;Dyno&#x201D; Don Nicholson, along with names such as Dave Strickler, Buddy Martin, Dick Harrell and John Zintsmaster, whose Kokomo, Indiana-based Zintsmaster Chevrolet, owned and ran the 1962 factory lightweight Impala that is being offered. This SS 409 was shipped to the Zintsmaster Chevrolet dealership in Kokomo, Indiana, and it survives with its documentation intact; some relating it&#x2019;s all too brief racing career. The current owner reports that this is the only known surviving factory-documented car. The Zintsmaster car is commonly recognized as the most original, factory-built lightweight that the respected experts of the marque know about. This Impala SS was raced by the Zintsmaster Chevrolet dealership in essentially the very state that it is now being presented; a virtual time capsule. The lightweight Impala SS was driven by Dave Mason, whose name is still painted on the door. Zintsmaster took this car to the 1962 U.S. Nationals at Indianapolis Raceway Park where Mr. Mason ran it in the low 12-second range at 115-mph down the famed quarter-mile strip. Shortly after that, the car was described as being retired from competition and placed in private storage, where it then remained out of sight for over 20 years. It is said that Mr. Zintsmaster kept the lightweight SS 409 with its documentation until 1988 when it first was sold into another private collection. The rare Ermine White Impala lightweight racecar remains fundamentally unchanged since it raced at the Indy Nationals. It preserves almost all its original paint, except for slight touch-ups. A Roman Red stripe runs the length of both sides and the Zintsmaster Chevrolet is advertised as &#x201C;Indiana&#x2019;s Fastest Trader.&#x201D; The original red bucket seat interior, the original whitewall tires from its last racing season, the original dual-quad 409-cid, 409-hp V-8 engine, and the original BorgWarner floor-mounted four-speed, plus the original 4.56:1 Posi-traction rear end are all part of this amazing platform. To add even more status, the engine was built by the legendary Bill Thomas, later of Cheetah fame. Today, the retired drag racer registers only 5,500 miles. The interior is a standard 1962 Impala SS layout with radio and heater delete, with a tachometer mounted on the dash. Color-keyed factory steel wheels are still with the car, as is the spare in the trunk and Zintsmaster Chevrolet sticker on the rear bumper. Along with the original window sticker, this important piece of automotive history is accompanied by numerous newspaper articles with race results. The Zintsmaster SS lightweight has also been featured in multiple magazine articles that further chronicles that it represents the best of the best, with its racing pedigree and originality intact and on display.</car>
  <car id="_184563969" price="189200">This beautiful Tuxedo Black Corvette is one of only 2,610 fitted with the 327-cid, 360-hp L84 fuel-injected V-8 engine; the most powerful engine option available. The engine also came from GM with a special cam and mechanical lifters. Coupled to a close-ratio four-speed manual transmission and Posi-traction rear end, this car was a dominate street racer in its day, accelerating from 0- to 60-mph in a mere 5.9-seconds. With a matching black interior, this Sting Ray also displays the desirable factory aluminum wheels with knock-off hubs, AM radio and whitewall tires. &#xA0;In 1963 Chevrolet introduced the one-year-only Corvette split-window coupe designed by Larry Shinoda under the styling direction of Bill Mitchell. The design was inspired by Mitchell's 1959 Stingray racer and the 1961 Mako Shark concept car. In addition to the rear split-window design, the 1963 Corvette featured faux hood vents, a pointed hood bulge or &#x201C;stinger,&#x201D; and a raised spine across the roof. These design elements were eliminated in 1964, making the 1963 model rare and desirable among collectors. &#xA0;The Corvette featured rear independent suspension designed by famed GM engineer Zora Arkus-Duntov. The Corvette also benefited from one of the greatest engines of all times, the 327-cid version of the Chevy &#x201C;small-block.&#x201D; Compact light and capable of staggering amounts of horsepower, it was also a relatively inexpensive engine. The 1963 Corvette was available in four engines options rated between 250- and 360-hp. Chevrolet built 21,513 Corvette Sting Rays in 1963. The production was a near-equal division between convertibles and split-window coupes.</car>
  <car id="_184564225" price="37400">Triple taillights tell us this is an Impala. Chevrolet wanted to be sure people knew you were driving the top-of-the-line, as lesser Chevies made do with dual taillights. The Impala name appeared for the first time in 1958 as a deluxe trim and appearance package on the Bel Air hardtop and convertible. It became a separate, top-of-the-line series in 1959. &#xA0;Big news for Chevrolet in 1964 was the all-new mid-size Chevelle, but the full-size Chevrolet remained the sales leader with 1.6 million sold. After all, why mess with a good thing? As such, the big Chevy received minor changes with an update on the new-for-1963 body shell: a more rounded look with a flatter grille and redesigned rear panel. &#xA0;The SS or Super Sport was considered a separate series for the first time rather than an Impala option package. In SS trim, this was one handsome car. The Impala quickly became the symbol for luxury and performance in the early sixties and introduced Chevrolet&#x2019;s signature &#x201C;SS&#x201D; brand of performance. &#xA0;A perfect example is this 409 Super Sport. It was definitely built with performance in mind with the 340 horsepower engine and a four-speed transmission. Features include bucket seats with center console, stainless tri-bar wheel covers, engine-turned trim on the rear cove molding, instrument panel and console; and discreet placement of SS badges on the exterior. &#xA0;Other options include the column-mounted tachometer, power steering, AM radio, trunk light and, most notably, the very rare vinyl top. Of the nearly 100,000 Impalas built for 1964, only 7,326 had this option, according to records. The body and paint reflect quality of a fresh restoration, and only minor pitting is found on some window trim. Overall, it is a very clean and striking triple black Impala that is dressed to impress.</car>
  <car id="_184564737" price="42900">The 1966 Corvette carried over much of the prior years&#x2019; designs with a few subtle changes. A Corvette script was now found on the hood, while the roof vents, previously both functional and non-functional, were deleted completely. The base engine was bumped from 250 horsepower up to 300. This little red Corvette sports a matching leather interior. It is equipped with power steering, power disc brakes, AM/FM radio, power antenna, telescoping steering wheel, clock and spinner wheel covers. The small-block V-8 engine is mated to a four-speed transmission. It is noted that the folding top, possibly original to the car, fits very well, but has minor defects. With newer paint, the fit and finish of this roadster makes for a very nice driver that can be enjoyed without worry.</car>
  <car id="_184564738" price="27500">The Chevy II, born as economical car with either a four or six cylinder engine was first offered for the 1962 model year. As the Chevy II developed, horsepower ratings increased, and styling changes were made each year. In 1966 the Chevy II/Nova was restyled in keeping with the bigger Chevrolet designs and Super Sport trim as well as V-8 engines were readily available. Equipped with a 327 small-block and an automatic transmission, this silver SS looks ready for a street race with its five-spoke Weld wheels. This Nova is very clean in every area, from the detailed engine compartment to the neat-as-a pin bucket seat interior. Notable features include headers, four-barrel carburetor, console, aftermarket performance gauges and the original AM radio. This is a perfect entry level option for anyone wanting to experience an easy to drive and enjoy musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_184564993" price="250250">1967 was the year that was not meant to be, at least not for the Sting Ray as we know it. Chevrolet had hoped to launch a brand new body style for this model year but concern about the aerodynamic efficiency of the new design caused its postponement. As is so often the case, this production glitch enabled the Sting Ray to evolve and, in the process, offer one of the most awesome cars to hit the road. Some would argue it was the best Corvette ever. The bodywork was given only a few cosmetic changes since it was not expected to remain in production, but major developments took place beneath the hood. Although the two small-block engines remained, still rated at 300 and 350 horsepower, big-block 427 cubic inch engines were rated as high as 435 horsepower as seen here. Showing just 5,900 original miles from new, this 100-percent original and non-restored time capsule is among the lowest mileage examples of the 427/435 Sting Rays in existence. Purchased new by a GM engineer, it was stored in a climate controlled environment for 40 years. This exceptionally original survivor wears the original and desirable Marlboro Maroon paint, original black interior, original drivetrain and engine compartment, chrome and stainless. Also included is the original tank sticker, Protect-O-Plate and a well-documented ownership history. A true benchmark automobile, it&#x2019;s impossible to duplicate options include L71 427-cid, 435-hp tri-power V-8, M21 close ratio four-speed transmission, Posi-traction axle, F41 special suspension, N11 off-road exhaust system, shoulder harness, transistor ignition, AM/FM radio and 775 x 15 redline tires. Having received multiple NCRS awards and Top Flight Status, this is an ultimate Blue-Chip Corvette that is worthy of the finest collection.</car>
  <car id="_184564994" price="137500">Having received a beautifully executed frame-off restoration, this handsome Corvette is not only finished in the popular Silver Pearl with black stinger and interior combination, it is driven by the desirable and fearsome 427-cid, 435-hp V-8 engine that has three two-barrel carbs and is mated to a four-speed manual transmission. The Corvette also has an AM radio, removable accessory hardtop, headrests, redline tires; power windows, brakes and steering.</car>
  <car id="_184565505" price="33000">Powered by a small-block V-8 engine that has performance accessories and is backed by an automatic transmission, this Camaro is finished in Rally Green with a black interior and has the RS and SS accessories, which includes the desirable hidden headlights. The car has bucket seats, console-shift, seatbelts, rear deck spoiler, back-up lights, front and rear bumper guards; pwer top, steering and disc brakes. The paint is absolutely beautiful and the soft-top is new. The Camaro also has the correct factory-style "hockey stick" accent stripes.</car>
  <car id="_184565506" price="77000">Chevrolet&#x2019;s first-generation Camaro facelift would serve the 1969 model year only. While major mechanical components were carried over from 1968, new sheetmetal, except the hood and trunk lid, gave the car a substantially sportier look. New door skins, rear quarter panels and rear valance panel also gave the car a much lower, wider and aggressive look. The RS option comprised a special black-painted grille with concealed headlights and headlight washers, fender striping, simulated rear fender louvers, front and rear wheel opening moldings, black body sill and more. "This is our mean streak," is how Chevrolet described its new-for-1969 Z28 in selected advertisements. In addition to the model's standard Turbo-Fire V-8 engine, buyers received quick-ratio steering, special suspension, Rally stripes, Z28 emblems and more. Mandatory options included power disc brakes and manual transmission with Hurst floor-mounted shifter. A full concours-quality rotisserie restoration has brought this vintage Camaro to the finest quality any collector could hope to find. It is presented as a Z28 with RS features, which includes the desirable and visually appealing covered headlights. Originally finished in green, it now wears a stunning black finish with optional and functional cowl hood and both front and rear spoilers. The drivetrain is a 302-cid V-8 engine and a four-speed transmission as prescribed by the Z28 package. Under the hood, everything is in place, down to the factory smog equipment, Delco battery, factory-type markings, plus proper GM hoses and clamps. It is a power brakes, non-power steering version and also has a Delco AM/FM radio. Goodyear bias-ply wide tread GT tires are mounted on all four corners with Rally wheels, while the deluxe black interior features a center console and Rally Pack gauges. Only 140 miles have been driven since completion on this best-of-the-best Camaros.</car>
  <car id="_184565507" price="25300">Popular muscle cars tend to become scarce when swept up by enthusiasts and investors. Collectors turn to other means to create the car of their dreams, which is where tribute cars often come from. As seen in this example, tributes can be as nice, or nicer than the factory offered. Dolled up as a SS396, this Camaro is actually fitted with a 454 big block V-8, high-rise manifold, headers, and a 400 Turbo automatic transmission. Other notable equipment to be found is a transmission cooler, power steering, power disc brakes, five-spoke aluminum mag wheels with Cooper radial tires, cowl induction hood and chin spoiler. From the sparkling blue finish to the Hugger Orange engine, it is detailed and ready for the show or street. This is an excellent version of the very popular &#x2019;69 Camaro.</car>
  <car id="_184565508" price="62700">This sensational 1969 Chevrolet twin-turbo &#x201C;Bomber Corvette&#x201D; was built by S/S Motorsports of Sarasota exclusively for the 2008 SEMA show. The car utilizes an original 1969 Corvette as the &#x201C;donor&#x201D; and has a tube chassis, C5 Corvette front suspension, independent rear suspension, fully-adjustable coil-over shocks and six-piston street/track ventilated four-wheel disc braking system. The wheels are custom S/S (18x9 front and 18x12 rear) with street/track tires. The drivetrain includes a custom built 565-cid (9.0-liter), 1,200-hp Dart&#xAE; S/S engine with twin turbochargers, fuel injection and runs on 93-octane pump fuel. It is further enhanced with Dart&#xAE; Pro 1 aluminum heads, S/S polished aluminum valve covers, custom fabricated intake manifold and high-capacity aluminum radiator. The transmission is a paddle-shift 4L80E automatic with overdrive. Among the exterior features is custom paint with S/S stripe, custom four-inch side exhaust with fabricated ceramic-coated headers, L88 hood, 24-gallon fuel tank, pop-top fuel cap, plus T-tops and removable rear window. The interior is laden with special details that include a custom billet steering wheel with leather, paddle-shifters with digital display, high-capacity air conditioning system with multi-directional vents, carbon fiber dash with aircraft-style toggle and momentary switches, carbon fiber center console, full gauge package with S/S custom faces and bomber aircraft-type bezels, black leather racing seats with black suede inserts, pushbutton electric start, navigation system with in-dash monitor and a sound-deadening package.</car>
  <car id="_184565509" price="39600">Don Yenko was a Chevrolet dealer in Pennsylvania, with much interest in performance. A big-time Chevy racer, he earned four SCCA national titles including 1962 and 1963 and in 1965 formed Yenko Sports Cars. He worked with GM and in 1969, which agreed to give Yenko access to cars with factory-installed L72 engines through Central Office Production Orders. This was a way past GM internal red-tape whereby a 427-cid motor (forbidden in the Camaro) could be installed without upper-management approval. Today, true Yenko COPO Camaros demand prices well into the six-figure range, and clones or tribute cars, as offered here, are a more affordable way to enjoy the looks and blazing performance. With 6,190 miles after restoration, this 427 V-8, 425 horsepower coupe is an awesome machine. It also has a Hurst short shifter for the four-speed, dual exhaust, 12-bolt differential, power steering, power disc brakes, and 15-inch American Racing mags mounted with new BFGoodrich Radial T/A tires. The standard black interior features an AM radio, Sun Super Tach II tachometer, oil pressure and water temp gauges. The engine compartment is restored to appear correct as a Yenko down to the hoses and clamps. A cowl induction hood, rear and front chin spoilers complete this great looking musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_184565761" price="91300">This Chevelle SS LS5 convertible is the beneficiary of a full body-off restoration. The body is &#x201C;laser-straight,&#x201D; and the undercarriage is also completed with meticulous detail in mind. The car is impeccably completed as no expense was spared on the refurbishment. The powerful car is ready to drive, with plenty of go. The Chevelle was built in the GM plant in Baltimore, Maryland and runs with the desirable 454-cid, 360-hp V-8 LS5 engine that has a four-barrel carburetor and is mated to a Turbo-Hydramatic 400 automatic transmission. The exhaust is a dual system with 2.5-inch diameter pipes from front-to-rear. The Chevelle carries its correct drivetrain with matching numbers. Among the many features that are found on this car is factory air conditioning; uncommonly seen on convertibles of this era. Additionally there is a Cowl Induction hood, hood lock-pins, tinted glass, AM radio, performance suspension, bucket seats, center console, power convertible top and power brakes. SS wheels, dual center stripes and SS badging all contribute to the muscle aspect of this exciting car. Climate-controlled storage is another solid positive for this desirable machine.</car>
  <car id="_184570881" price="10175">The SS 454 pickup was a performance variant of the 1500-Series 1/2-ton truck produced by Chevrolet from 1990 through 1993. It was introduced to the public on September 1, 1989 and later inspired the production of its competitor, the Ford Lightning, in 1993. The SS 454 was a rather rare truck, as only 16,953 were produced in three years. Power is supplied by a &#x201C;big-block&#x201D; 454-cid V-8 producing 230-hp at 3,600-rpm and 385 foot-pounds of torque at 1,600-rpm. It is equipped with a three-speed automatic transmission and 3.73:1 rear axle ratio. Inside, bucket seats replaced the standard bench seat. &#xA0;Nicely detailed underhood, this sinister black truck features a contrasting red cloth interior, power windows and door locks, AM/FM stereo radio, cassette tape deck, tilt steering wheel and integral bedliner.</car>
  <car id="_201339393" price="40150">The Chrysler 300B introduced for 1956 was similar to the previous year&#x2019;s inaugural 300. It did, however, benefit from a revised tailfin treatment, as well as a new engine rated at 340 brake horsepower, a significant boost over the previous year&#x2019;s offering of 300 brake horsepower. This second Chrysler 300 appeared around 12 months after the introduction of the C-300 and was again based on the New Yorker body with an Imperial grille, heavy-duty suspension and high performance hemi 354-cid V-8 engine. Styling and power refinements were seen, resulting in a modernized look, added muscle under the hood, plus a more civilized demeanor. The majority of the styling changes were shared with other Chrysler models and technical modifications centered on increased engine displacement, pushbutton automatic transmissions and the introduction of floating shoe, center-plane brakes. The impressive engine made the 300B the most powerful American car available. &#xA0;Finished in Black with beige interior and black carpet, this 300B has been with the same owner for the last 35 years. It is reported by the current vendor to be the only similar car with factory air conditioning. While it is stated that the unit is complete, it is not currently in working order. The detailed engine compartment reflects a great deal of originality, plus the Chrysler runs and drives &#x201C;as it should.&#x201D; The interior has had reproduction seat covers added, but this was executed prior to the1990 purchase by the current vendor. The 300B has a replacement headliner from Gary Goers. Along with exceptional brightwork detail; additional equipment found on this uncommon beauty includes a two-speed PowerFlite automatic transmission, AM radio, a heater and power windows. This 300B rides on standard steel wheels shod with whitewall tires and checkered-style factory full wheel covers. Only 1,102 similar cars were produced in the 1956 model year.</car>
  <car id="_218123265" price="29700">The DeLorean DMC-12 sports car was the dream of John DeLorean, former General Manager of the Pontiac Division of General Motors. The car was built for the American market in 1981-1982 featuring novel gullwing doors with a fiberglass "underbody" to which non-structural brushed stainless steel panels were affixed. The car became iconic for its appearance in the movie Back to the Future as a modified time machine as well as for the trials and tribulations of founder John DeLorean. The prototype appeared in October 1976 and production began in 1981 in Northern Ireland with the first DMC-12 rolling off the production line on January 21. &#xA0;Approximately 9,000 DMC-12s were made before production halted in early 1983.This five-speed DeLorean with power windows, power seats, cassette tape player and air conditioning has just 6,256 miles and is noted to be in great condition.</car>
  <car id="_234894337" price="88000">The Devin Special is a serious sports car. It has a tube frame, lightweight fiberglass body, aluminum interior, complete instrumentation, individual windscreens, functional hoodscoop, aluminum headrest, &#x201C;eggcrate&#x201D; grille, quick-fill fuel cap and sport mirrors. The Devin is finished in white and blue which represented American racing colors of the period; such as seen on the respected Cunningham team. &#xA0;This exciting open cockpit two-seater was produced by Devin Enterprises in El Monte, California. This particular car is powered by a Chevrolet 283-cid V-8 engines with dual Carter AFB carburetors with an original Bill Devin dual four-barrel aluminum intake that Mr. Devin designed and cast himself. The owner reports that only around 15 of these components are known to exist. This unit is hooked up to a Muncie aluminum four-speed manual transmission and a Ford nine-inch rear end. The transmission has a Hurst shifter that is also stated to be &#x201C;super rare.&#x201D; The current owner contacted Hurst about the shifter, and sent them a photograph, as he had never seen a similar one. The Hurst people, he conveys, immediately attempted to buy the shifter as it was described to him as one of approximately 100 produced by Hurst in the 1960s. Despite a very generous offer, it remains with the Devin. &#xA0;The exhaust is routed through large side pipes. Equipped with Ansen PIN drive wheels and correct Vintage Dunlop racing tires as it was in 1958. The chassis is set up with adjustable coil-over shocks up front and dual shock absorbers on both rear corners. The front brakes are discs and the rear has drums. This historically important car has only about 200 miles on a complete "period correct" professional restoration. The prior owner told the current vendor that the Devin was rescued from a barn in California. &#xA0; The 1950s produced a unique time in American sports car racing. The ever-growing popularity of road racing in Southern California soon attracted independent car builders who embodied the inventive spirit and skill of the hot rod culture. Homemade specials began to challenge, and on occasion, beat the Ferraris, Jaguars and Maseratis. &#xA0;Bill Devin was part of that scene, and out of this setting he created the Devin Special. Devin also manufactured fiberglass bodies to fit a wide variety of chassis&#x2019;, giving talented hobbyists the opportunity to build their own sports car at a fraction of the cost.</car>
  <car id="_251671041" price="24200">Being offered is this beautifully restored Coronet that is presented in a very attractive tri-color paint scheme. This is reported as a low mileage car that has a a primarily original interior that includes patterned two-tone upholstery, pushbutton automatic transmission, AM radio and clock, The car also is equipped with a Red Ram V-8 engine, Kelsey-Hayes chrome wire wheels, dual antennas, dual mirrors and whitewall tires - all wrapped into a handsomely styled two-door hardtop design.</car>
  <car id="_251674369" price="61600">With musclecar mania near its peak, Chrysler Corporation, presumably realizing that its powerful engines and racing success had not yet given it leadership in muscle sales, inaugurated the Scat Pack for Dodge, which was successful enough to be copied as the Rapid Transit System for Plymouth. When introduced in 1968, the Scat Pack included the Charger R/T, Coronet R/T, Dart GTS, Swinger 340 and Super Bee as promoted in print ads, brochures, a national club, decals and swag. Mid-year 1969 presented the Scat Pack with a whole new level of performance in the A12 Super Bee.</car>
  <car id="_251674625" price="42900">Dodge first introduced the Charger as a mid-year addition to its 1966 lineup. It shared much of its sheetmetal and underpinnings with the Coronet. In 1968, the Charger was restyled creating quite the sensation on the showroom floor for its combination of good looks, outstanding performance and great value. 1970 marked the third and final year for this bodystyle on Dodge&#x2019;s intermediate Charger of which the division produced 10,337 R/T&#x2019;s. R/T simply meant Road/Track which also meant business to Dodge&#x2019;s competitors. The 1970 received non-functional scoops bolted on to each door to highlight the sporty theme. This red R/T with white vinyl top and white pinstripes over a white vinyl bucket seat/console-equipped interior with black carpets makes for a perfect overall combination. The nicely detailed engine bay is equipped with 440 Magnum V-8 and TorqueFlite automatic transmission. Other extras include Code W23 road wheels, AM radio, power steering and brakes.</car>
  <car id="_251676673" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_285214209" price="66000">Charles &#x201C;Fred&#x201D; Dunbar was a skilled machinist. In the late 1800s, he went to work for Charles Cretors in Chicago, Illinois, as a head machinist. Cretors, the inventor of a steam corn-popping machine and a showman at heart, was having great success with a wagon that incorporated his popping and peanut roasting machinery with a small steam engine. Children and adults alike were transfixed, and sales were immense. &#xA0;As time went on, Dunbar and Cretors more and more frequently came into conflict, as each possessed a strong personality. Mr. Cretors&#x2019; son was able to intercede in many cases, but in 1902, when it came out that Fred Dunbar was developing a hot-air corn popper, the gloves came off. Dunbar was summarily sent packing. &#xA0;Undaunted, Fred Dunbar moved down the street from his former boss and continued to work under the shingle of Dunbar &amp; Company. When Cretors moved to another location the following year, Dunbar took over his old quarters. Over the next few years, Dunbar advertised not only popcorn equipment, but also gas lighting for homes and even automotive work, although the latter is believed to have involved just a few cars built to customer order. The firm also repaired and rebuilt a number of automobiles around 1904. The centennial history of Cretors that was published in 1985 acknowledges that the loss of Fred Dunbar set the company back many years. &#xA0;Dunbar&#x2019;s air popping, however, proved to be advantageous for producing large quantities of popcorn in anticipation of future sales. The corn emerged from the popper dry, and it was kept fresh longer. A special Dunbar-patented automatic buttering devise buttered the popcorn as the customer purchased it. Thus, it became the favored method for locations such as movie houses and fairs, and they experienced surges of sales. Snack foods were neither as prevalent nor as varied as today, so Dunbar and Cretors competed fiercely during the first half of the 20th century. Both companies survive today: Cretors manufactures equipment for the production and preparation of a large variety of hot and cold snack foods, while Dunbar Manufacturing maintains a substantial business in air poppers of Fred Dunbar&#x2019;s 1900 principle, which are now made from stainless steel. &#xA0;Offered here is the only known restored Model 1200 Dunbar Popcorn Wagon with correct interior and exterior and original steam-operating equipment to survive. Nine others are extant, but they have either been extensively modified, with their steam equipment being removed and replaced with modern poppers, or they have been fitted with balloon tires or mounted on automobile chassis for greater mobility. This unit has had but three owners in 34 years. From 1979 to 2001, when it was purchased by the current owner, it remained in Cedar Rapids, Iowa. &#xA0;Following acquisition, the current owner submitted it to a full and comprehensive restoration over a period of 12 years, with much historical assistance from Dunbar experts Bruce and Darlene Anderson. The restoration was undertaken with the cooperation of craftsmen at Anderson Restoration and Jordan Engineering, as well as Mark Owens, Denny Farrington, Antique Service Center, Jerry Sweet and Owen Franks. &#xA0;A complete set of engineering drawings was made, from an original machine in some cases, to aid in the restoration and fabrication of missing parts. The Wagon was completely stripped and correctly refinished in natural varnished oak, inside and out. The ceiling is done in green with yellow, red and gold ornamentation. It has the characteristic Dunbar-vaulted roof over the front section, which houses twin air poppers on the left and the steam engine across the front. The engine is mounted behind glass and at eye level, to catch and hold the attention of children. The engine, piping, and accessories are polished nickel plate, while the vending windows slide down in tracks to allow complete open-air access. The equipment is correct and complete, including the Dunbar buttering device, which was patented on November 26, 1907. &#xA0;The wheels and undercarriage are painted in bright yellow, and the roof exterior is painted in handsome maroon. The engineering drawings from the restoration and a color reprint of the illustrated factory catalogue are included in the sale, as well as photos of the restoration and a one-horse hitch. Fully functional and operational, this rare Model D Dunbar Popcorn Wagon is ideal for display at a parade or carnival.</car>
  <car id="_302008833" price="29150">1980 saw the arrival of the Excalibur Series IV, the model of Excalibur that brought about the first real change in appearance of the marque. It was also the first Excalibur to have glass side windows, a trunk/boot integrated within the bodywork and an electrically operated soft-top for the phaeton, as well as roadster models. The chassis, especially unchanged relative to the Series III's, was again stretched, this time by 13 inches. The styling had also evolved. It still undeniably evoked vintage Mercedes-Benz, but this time emulated the 500/540K series rather than the SS/SSK. This Series IV Phaeton utilizes a 350-cid General Motors V-8 engine and is also equipped with an automatic transmission. Although the performance continued to be decreased due to ever-increasing Federal requirements, the buying public seemed to readily accept this as they appeared more concerned with comfort and appointments than out-and-out performance dynamics. &#xA0;The silver with black Excalibur Series IV Phaeton that is being offered has been in the same family since 1987 and is in original condition with 50,000 actual miles. It has power steering, power brakes, power windows, a radio with cassette tape player and both a hardtop and soft-top that are presented in black. &#xA0;Additional features include chrome wire wheels, dual spotlights, dual side-mounted spares, faux external exhaust and integral trunk.</car>
  <car id="_318784257" price="605000">Introduced as the replacement to the 275 GTB/4, Ferrari&#x2019;s 365 GTB/4 took the company&#x2019;s styling in a whole new direction. While the 275&#x2019;s styling featured voluptuous lines and curves, the Scaglietti bodywork on the 365 GTB/4 was noticeably more sharp and angular, yet still achingly gorgeous. Though Enzo Ferrari furiously squashed any official use of the Daytona moniker after the name was inadvertently leaked to the press, it remains in popular use to this day, forever commemorating Ferrari&#x2019;s 1-2-3 finish at the 1967 24 Hours of Daytona. Revered by tifosi and general sports car aficionados alike, the 365 GTB/4 is particularly notable as the last of Maranello&#x2019;s legendary vintage V-12 road cars. Bestowed with a 4.4-liter V-12 engine mated to six Weber carburetors and a five-speed transaxle, the Daytona produced 352-hp and with a top speed of 174-mph, it was labeled as the fastest production sports car in the world. While the price of the Daytona rose from $19,500 to $23,940 over the course of the Daytona&#x2019;s five-year production run; its appeal certainly never diminished. The Daytona went on to become the best-selling V-12 Ferrari of the vintage era and a grand total of 1,273 were produced from 1968-1973. Sadly, this would be Ferrari&#x2019;s last front engined-two seat grand tourer until the introduction of the 550 Maranello in 1996. Completed by the factory on February 6th, 1973 according to noted Ferrari historian Marcel Massini, this Daytona was delivered new to Pedini Automobili S.a.s., located in Perugia, Italy. The car was finished in Rosso Chiaro (20-R-190) over Beige (VM 3218) leather, and is fitted with factory air conditioning. Sometime after the car was sold to its first owner by Pedini Automobili, this Daytona was exported to the United States. In 1987, it was shipped back to Italy for a complete restoration and returned to the United States shortly thereafter. While residing with its current owner in Canada, this Daytona recently had its brake system fully rebuilt in addition to a full mechanical service and compression check, the results of which are on file for further inspection. The interior, fitted with red leather &#x201C;Daytona inserts&#x201D; in the seats, matching red carpets, black leather dashboard, and a Nardi wood-rimmed steering wheel, is warm and inviting and would be a fantastic place to be for both driver and passenger on long road trips with the seats showing only slight wear from previous enjoyment. Sporting Campagnolo alloy wheels with knock-off hubs as per factory spec, this Daytona would be instantly recognizable to a bystander as a Ferrari, whether at speed or standing still. The Daytona is without a doubt one of Ferrari&#x2019;s most iconic front-engined GT cars and almost all tifosi aspire to have a Daytona in their collection. They are cars that are just as exciting to drive as they are comfortable, and were perfect when new for jaunts across Europe and the United States, and remain so to this day. The Daytona presented here is indeed an excellent example of the breed, featuring an always desirable color combination and a recent servicing. It is undoubtedly ready to return to the open road.</car>
  <car id="_318788353" price="10000">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_318791425" price="77000">Introduced in 1996, the 550 was not unlike the early Ferrari Daytona as a front engined V-12 two-seat grand touring car. By the end of the model run in 2002, 3,083 550s had been produced. Prominently colored in Fly Yellow with rouge (dark red) leather upholstery, this Maranello is sure to stand out in any crowd of Italian sports cars. The interior is in tip-top shape, with the soft seats piped in yellow. With such features as air conditioning, power seats, power windows, remote mirrors and CD sound system, this Ferrari has it all. The 485 horsepower V-12 is impressive at any speed and the six-speed manual transmission is a thrill to operate. Other notable points include the 18-inch alloy wheels with Pirelli tires and the original books and manuals that are included. With just 30,410 kilometers, (18,895 miles) from new, this Ferrari is ready for the next Italiano Concorso.</car>
  <car id="_335550465" price="29150">The late 1930&#x2019;s Fords were ground breaking in many ways by the sleek and stylish design was a huge departure from the past. Aerodynamics was now a consideration in building a car, as was the ever-growing European influence. Taking Ford&#x2019;s sleek design to the next level, this attractive burnt orange coupe has seen a tremendous amount of custom fabrication. The top has been chopped, door handles shaved, spotlights added and many other subtle alterations are seen. The hand-crafted white interior is equipped with a power windows and locks, Pioneer AM/FM/CD/XM sound system, CB, Infinity speakers, as well as Auto Meter gauges and a tilt steering column with &#x2019;59 Chevy wheel. A small block V-8, topped with a Cadillac &#x201C;batwing&#x201D; air cleaner sits within the gleaming engine compartment. From top to bottom, this Ford is an excellent example of modern craftsmanship with a vintage flair.</car>
  <car id="_335551233" price="71500">This Ford Roadster Custom is driven by a General Motors LS1 350-cid V-8 engine that is mated to a 4L60L overdrive transmission with a Lokar shifter. The rear end is a nine-inch Ford with a quick-change cover. The exhaust note is courtesy of street and performance headers that are routed through 2.5-inch polished stainless steel exhaust. The engine compartment is immaculate and exhibits paint features found on the bodywork.&#xA0; &#xA0;The car is based on a Coast to Coast frame with a triangulated four-link rear suspension, Kugel Komponents polished front suspension, Kugel rack-and-pinion steering and Wilwood polished brake system. The Ford runs with Colorado Custom Super Max wheels and Dunlop tires with complementary front-to-rear sizes that create just the right stance. The roadster is finished in PPG DBC Black with custom air-brushed true fire flames. The interior features Hot Sauce Red ultra-leather interior that was executed by Bitchen Stichen, and it is also seen in the trunk area. The dash is fitted with TPI gauges and a Colorado Custom steering wheel. &#xA0;This exceptional machine has won the PPG Dream Car Award and has been a winner of the Best of Show Award at 12 different local shows. The Ford is stored, when not in use, in a climate-controlled environment.</car>
  <car id="_335551234" price="70400">After making automotive history in 1932 with the introduction of the new Ford V-8, the Ford Motor Company embarked on a completely redesigned automobile for the 1933 model year. While the 1932 was a landmark vehicle in terms of its flathead engine, its exterior design closely resembled the Model A Ford. The 1933 Fords used the mechanical elements of the 1932s but completely changed the exterior of the vehicle to become what many consider to one of the most iconic vehicles of the 1930s. &#xA0;The new &#x201C;Model 40&#x201D; was built on a longer, 112&#x201D; wheelbase chassis that was redesigned with a double drop on both the front and rear and a modified X-member. The grill was completely redesigned with rear-angled bars-a key design element was repeated in the hood and windshield. Fully skirted fenders and a significantly lower body line made the 1933 Fords appear long, sleek and forwardly aggressive. &#xA0;It&#x2019;s no wonder why the 1933 Fords are considered automotive icons today not only be restorers but by hot rodders as well. &#xA0;John Marchman of Houston Texas appreciated the clean lines of Ford&#x2019;s 1933 roadster when he set out to build this outstanding hotrod, well known by today&#x2019;s hotrod enthusiasts as the &#x201C;Mexican Blackbird.&#x201D; &#xA0;Marchman started with an original 1933 Ford all steel roadster body. He then began to collect period speed equipment, saving the rarest and most desirable components for the build of this hot rod. Marchman not only wanted his car to look right, but to drive right as well. The power plant would come from a 276 cubic inch flathead Ford engine that would be extensively rebuilt and modified using a Winfield camshaft on the inside and Johnson lifters. The engine was then topped with a desirable SCOT supercharger, which was fuel by twin Stromberg 97 carburetors and a set of finned, aluminum high compression heads. The three-speed transmission is engaged via a 1940 Ford column shifter and is packed with a desirable Lincoln Zephyr gear cluster. To enable the car to drive at highway speeds, a rare Columbia two-speed rear end was added and to stop the car, 1940 Lincoln hydraulic brakes were used. The chassis was stabilized with torsion bars, which would enable the car to have great handling characteristics. A dropped front axle and rare set of metal artillery wheels were added with traditional &#x201C;big and little&#x201D; black-wall tires which gave the car an aggressive stance. &#xA0;The original Ford body was finished in a conservative black paint scheme. The interior was also a nod to simplicity and was finished in brown hides and complemented by a tan folding top. &#xA0;The dash is equipped with a scarce and matching set of Stewart Warner gauges and rare police speedometer adorns the steering column. To add a finished touch, noted rock and roll legend and hot rod collector Billy Gibbons signed and dated the dashboard. A great color photo of Gibbons inside the Blackbird will accompany the sale. &#xA0;The Mexican Blackbird is both a nod to tradition and style. It is an aggressive, all-out hot rod suitable for a variety of events and would certainly be the focal point of any important American car collection.</car>
  <car id="_335552001" price="25025">Some old cars simply have, &#x201C;the look.&#x201D; This three-window coupe&#x2019;s proportions are fantastic from every angle. Built with an all-fiberglass body, this custom has managed to capture a modern twist on a vintage hot rod motif. The modern GM V-8 engine is topped with an Edelbrock dual-quad manifold with dual exhaust, Weber carburetors, headers and billet valve covers. Tan and red cloth was chosen for the seat and door panels in the comfy interior that also includes a GM tilt column with banjo wheel, power windows, AM/FM/CD system, TPI Tech gauges, vintage tach under the dash and a floor-shifted five-speed. Other highlights include a dropped front axle, American Racing wheels, and a hidden fuel cell beneath the rumbleseat lid. Dolled up with vintage graphics and pinstripes, it is a vintage hot rod look with all the modern touches.</car>
  <car id="_335552257" price="36300">1930s Fords are among the most desired among hot-rodders and restomod builders due to their high style and good looks. This tan Deluxe Coupe with subtle red pinstripes is certainly no exception. Equipped with a GM 350-cid crate engine and automatic transmission; further modifications include a nine-inch Ford rear end and Edelbrock performance manifolds and Sanderson headers. Inside you find chocolate leather seats, white-faced gauges, Vintage heat, and a custom sound system. The suspension has lowered springs giving it a gently raked stance. Red Coker wheels are fitted with wide whitewalls tires adding to the period look.</car>
  <car id="_335552513" price="29150">The late 1930&#x2019;s Fords were ground breaking in many ways by the sleek and stylish design was a huge departure from the past. Aerodynamics was now a consideration in building a car, as was the ever-growing European influence. Taking Ford&#x2019;s sleek design to the next level, this attractive burnt orange coupe has seen a tremendous amount of custom fabrication. The top has been chopped, door handles shaved, spotlights added and many other subtle alterations are seen. The hand-crafted white interior is equipped with a power windows and locks, Pioneer AM/FM/CD/XM sound system, CB, Infinity speakers, as well as Auto Meter gauges and a tilt steering column with &#x2019;59 Chevy wheel. A small block V-8, topped with a Cadillac &#x201C;batwing&#x201D; air cleaner sits within the gleaming engine compartment. From top to bottom, this Ford is an excellent example of modern craftsmanship with a vintage flair.</car>
  <car id="_335556097" price="42900">This 1952 Ford F-1 Custom all-steel pickup has the original cab, fenders, frame and dash board. A smoothy box and steel running boards were installed. The frame was modified to accommodate a Heidst Mustang II front end and airbag suspension. The Ford was completed over a two-year period.&#xA0; The power is produced by a &#x201C;Jim Pace Pontiac&#x201D; crate HO deluxe 350-cid small block 330-hp V-8 engine. This four-bolt main engine, with a nodular iron crank, PM steel rods, cast aluminum pistons and Vortek heads, teamed with a patterned cam, resonates great sound with performance. The custom high performance radiator was made by Griffin Thermal Products. The hand-made aluminum drive shaft is fully balanced. The water pump, alternator, air conditioner pump and serpentine pulleys are all polished aluminum. Mooneyes furnished the engine dress-up items. The engine was bolted to a 700R transmission, using a Corvette 2000 stall torque converter. The shifter linkage, brake and gas pedals were ordered from Lokar. The exhaust system was custom was made and stainless mufflers were installed. &#xA0;Vintage Air conditioning, Ididit steering column, power steering, power brakes, power windows, remote doors and Billit handles are all utilized on this quality build. Nitro 555 extreme tires were mounted on Budnik one-off polished aluminum wheels, made specifically for the measured offsets of this truck. These measure 17.7-inches in front and 18.8 on the rear. &#xA0;The chassis modifications were completed by St. Lucie Auto Body in Florida. The interior upholstery and fabrication was done at Chewy&#x2019;s Interior Design in Jupiter, Florida. &#xA0;The fit, finish and paint work was completed by Doug Klann&#x2019;s, &#x201C;Slims Auto Works&#x201D; in Freeland, Michigan.</car>
  <car id="_335556865" price="110000">Original items of note that went into the O&#x2019;Mahoney car included: the frame, the rare and original Ford heavy duty dual outlet radiator, the original windshield with Bonneville 1961 &#x201C;Safety Inspected&#x201D; sticker, the rare &#x2019;57 Ford Spicer Limited Slip differential, the complete front and rear suspension assemblies, the T-10 four-speed close ratio gearbox, Stewart Warner gauges including Jaeger eight day clock, the bucket seats, the Halibrand 5-1/2-inch knock-off magnesium wheels, the finned Lincoln Pan American racing brakes, the 1961 Bonneville timing tag, and, of course, the original modified Y-block engine. &#xA0;The Y-block engine was torn down, completely rebuilt, bored and stroked resulting in a displacement of 322 cubic inches. New cylinder heads were obtained and Doane radically changed the valve angles and stagger on both the intakes and exhausts. The engine was topped with dual Holley carburetors and a Spencer-built custom aluminum air intake. Other engine modifications included a Holley NASCAR racing ignition system with a mechanical tach drive, a Mellings oil pump, and a Spencer-built custom oil sump and custom exhaust system. &#xA0;The entire project took close to two years and cost well into six figures. Road tests deemed the new car quicker than the original. &#xA0; Almost as quickly as Mahoney took delivery, Kirk White began an aggressive attempt to purchase the Thunderbird. During this time, the car earned national publicity and was featured in &#x201C;Rod &amp; Custom&#x201D; in April of 1992, once again in April of 1993 and later Hot Rod Magazine&#x2019;s swimsuit edition. Finally, O&#x2019;Mahoney agreed with White to discuss the purchase of the Thunderbird. After a spirited test drive, an agreement was reached and the car became part of the Kirk White collection. &#xA0;Upon joining the White collection, the car was campaigned at a variety of driving events and concours where it has been multiple award winner and has always remained a bulletproof runner. &#xA0;In the flesh, the Thunderbird masquerades behind a thin veil of civility. With the slightest prodding, its wicked reality quickly surfaces.</car>
  <car id="_335559681" price="35000">Powered by a mildly modified 302-cid, 335-hp Windsor V-8 engine mated to an AOD transmission with overdrive, this attractive Mustang Convertible GT 350 tribute also features T-Bird taillights with White Pearl and black accessory Pony interior trim, Ford white face gauges, wood dash applique, three-spoke steering wheel and AM/FM stereo cassette radio. Finished in Cadillac White Diamond with GT trim and a black powered convertible top, this Mustang is sure to please while cruising down the highway. Additional modifications under the hood consist of a 625-cfm Demon carburetor and a 2500 stall converter among others. With rack-and-pinion power steering with dual torque boxes, progressive front coil springs and Edelbrock shocks, it is reported to be a fun car to drive with no reported squeaks or rattles.</car>
  <car id="_335559937" price="36300">The mid-size Fairlane changed little for 1967 except for a modest update of its front end styling. As a companion to the Fairlane GT series, the 500XL offered more luxury trim and a bit less emphasis on sportiness. Very rare when new and even more so today, just 1,943 convertibles were produced. 500XL&#x2019;s included all-vinyl bucket seats with center console and special rocker panel moldings. &#xA0;This 500XL is equipped with the extra cost 320-hp, 390-cid V-8 and four-speed manual transmission, dual exhaust, power steering, power-operated top, AM radio and added gauges under the dash. Its Frost Turquoise exterior is noted to be in good condition as is the trim. It is fitted with a black convertible top and matching aqua vinyl interior.</car>
  <car id="_335560449" price="176000">On offer is this fully restored, very correct example of Ford's preeminent musclecar; the highly respected Boss 429 with 375-hp from its renowned V-8 engine paired off with a four-speed manual transmission. Handsomely presented in Royal Maroon with black interior, this model is built on the SportsRoof platform. This exciting car conveys nothing but performance. You immediately notice the massive functional hood scoop, slightly modified (by the factory) wheel wells to accommodate the one-inch additional tire tread width, subtle front and rear spoilers, dual racing mirrors and chrome-plated Magnum 500 wheels. The high-back bucket seats are separated by a center console, and a radio is also aboard. The restoration has resulted in an engine compartment and undercarriage that is highly detailed. The engine block is stamped with correct partial VIN, and the transmission plus the remainder of the driveline are believed by the vendor to be original. The interior is correct with accurate non-toe pad carpet, while the trunk-mounted battery is an accurate reproduction with the proper vent caps. The engine has only a few hundred miles on an older professional rebuild. The steering system has a fresh rebuild with correct, unique Boss 429 parts; including ram, pump and Blue Dot reproduction hoses. Other evidence of the detail used in the restoration includes the use of correct reproduction Autolite shocks, correct date-coded glass, original-style lug nuts, alternator, belts and engine pulleys. All smog equipment is present. This exceptional example comes with a Deluxe Marti report, original factory build sheet, two Ford Dealer invoices (Eminger), 2013 MCA Concours inspection report, N.O.S. owner&#x2019;s manual, receipts and paperwork dating back to late 1980s. It also received the Concours &#x201C;trailered-driven&#x201D; Silver award at the 2013 MCA Grand National show, a fine verification to its pedigree.</car>
  <car id="_335560705" price="48950">Ford designated 1970 as the last year for the Boss and this is a solid representation of this iconic American musclecar. Powered by the renowned Boss 302-cid, 290-hp V-8 engine and backed by a sports-type four-speed manual transmission with Hurst shifter that are original to the car; this vehicle comes complete with an Elite Marti Report. &#xA0;Ford designated 1970 as the last year for the Boss and this is a solid representation of this iconic American musclecar. Powered by the renowned Boss 302-cid, 290-hp V-8 engine and backed by a sports-type four-speed manual transmission with Hurst shifter that are original to the car; this vehicle comes complete with an Elite Marti Report.</car>
  <car id="_335560706" price="74800">Introduced in 1964, the Mustang created a sensation in the media and in Ford showrooms across the country. It offered a winning combination of sporty performance, personal luxury, and fresh styling that turned out to be a direct hit on a previously unknown market segment. The result was the most successful new car introduction in the history of the automobile industry. Ford&#x2019;s Mustang triggered competition from every major car company, creating overnight the &#x201C;pony car&#x201D; class. Part of Mustang&#x2019;s appeal &#x2013; in addition to its lean size and sparkling performance &#x2013; was the broad options list. A buyer could specify anything from a spartan six-cylinder coupe to a top-of-the-line fully equipped V-8 convertible. In the late Sixties it seemed like horsepower would keep growing forever. Racing was on every manufacturer&#x2019;s agenda and promoting the brand through performance was a way of life in Detroit; possibly no manufacturer did it on a bigger international stage than Ford Motor Company due to their participation and winning at LeMans and other races of the FIA World Sportscar Championship, Formula One by financing the soon-to-become-legendary Ford Cosworth DFV engine, and continued pursuit of victories in the USAC National Championship and its premier event, the Indianapolis 500. Ford ceased its official racing activities in 1970, but not before they won the Trans Am title in a Bud Moore-prepared Mustang Boss 302 that was driven by teammates Parnelli Jones and George Follmer. The Mach 1 also was triumphant in the SCCA Manufacturer&#x2019;s Rally Championship. This showed the great versatility of the Mustang Mach 1 platform in that it ran over 8,000 total rallying miles on all kinds of roads in all kinds of weather and finish every grueling stage with split-second precision. In real world terms, it had to have sprint-like acceleration, holding a tight line when cornering, brakes that won&#x2019;t fade and have the power to ram your way through clogged mountain passes. The Mach 1 won these rallys because of mechanical attributes that includes a balanced wide-track chassis, sports car suspension design with front and rear stabilizer bars, heavy-duty springs and shocks, plus wide-rim wheels. Today, the 1969-1970 Mustangs are one of hottest market segments. With eye-catching examples like the Mach 1 offered here, it is easy to see why, especially the fact that this is one of the special cars that received the rare Super Cobra Jet engines. The R-code 428 SCJ was first presented during the 1969 model year. Mustang customers who selected either of the optional 3.91:1 or 4.30:1 rear end gear ratios got more than an optional axle feature. Ordering either of these axle ratio options commonly prompted a few other upgrades as well, including the 428 Super Cobra Jet engine, an external oil cooler located in front of the radiator, and relocation of the driver's side horn to the passenger side of the radiator core support to make room for the oil cooler. Beginning in February 1969 this complete package could be ordered as the "Drag Pack" option with the modified 428 cubic inch Super Cobra Jet engine. It is reported that the basic strength of the Super Cobra Jet engine is in a more durable assembly of the crank, rods, pistons, flywheel/flexplate and harmonic balancer. This redesign was calculated to withstand the higher RPM requisites of drag racing. Show quality is an understatement when describing this rotisserie restored SCJ Mach 1. It is finished in the exciting period color of Grabber Blue and comes with a black interior; it is picture perfect in its handsome presentation. From the proper primer finish on the undercarriage to the highly-detailed engine compartment with smog equipment and hose clamps, stickers and chalk marks all in the right places, it is hardly possible to fault the outstanding appearance. This Mustang was delivered from the factory as a 428 cubic inch Ram Air Super Cobra Jet Mach 1 rated at 335 horsepower. Among the many additional features that came with this exceptional car is the sought-after console-mounted four-speed manual transmission. Many consider this to be the source of the &#x201C;magic&#x201D; that comes with driving a musclecar such as this. Additional features are found with power steering, no power brakes, AM/FM system and Magnum 500 wheels shod with Firestone Wide O Oval tires. The front end design displayed a bold new grille, grille-mounted lamps, sport hood latches, &#x201C;shaker&#x201D; hood and a new black hood treatment. You will also see dual color-keyed racing mirrors, integral rear deck spoiler and front chin spoiler. Inside, there are many extra niceties that include woodgrain applique on the console, dash and door panels, high-back bucket seats, Sport Deck rear seat, factory radio and a deluxe three-spoke Rim-Blow steering wheel. The driver&#x2019;s side mirror also has remote adjustment. The exceptional restoration also includes excellent chrome and trim, and laser-straight body panels with well-aligned gaps. Nothing was left to want on this marvelous musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_335560961" price="51150">Among the rarest Ford musclecars is the Torino Cobra. This example is one of 3,054 Torino Cobras produced in 1971 and one of 408 in Grabber Green Metallic. It is powered by the 370 horsepower 429-CID four-barrel V-8, which is mated to a four-speed close-ratio transmission. The engine is reported to be original to the car. Other key features making this a blue chip investment Ford includes the Shaker hood scoop, rear window slats, Traction-Lok axle, Hurst shifter, highback bucket seats, console, power steering, power disc brakes, AM radio, power windows, front and rear bumper guards and tinted glass all around. Not only is this a rare piece of Ford history, it is also in pristine condition. It represents a very special opportunity not to be missed.</car>
  <car id="_352335873" price="35200">The Jeep remains the most iconic vehicle of World War II. It is the myth and symbol of liberation. Copies and variations of the U.S. military Jeep have been produced in many countries including this Hotchkiss M201 type for the French army. Reportedly 27,000 copies were created through 1966, as well as civilian units. In France, it is usually simply called, &#x201C;La Jeep.&#x201D; &#xA0;The M201 employs a simple conventional structure, designed around a light metal frame with two rigid axles suspended on leaf springs. It has been fully restored to the finest level in a U.S. Army livery with all of the extra niceties including a drop-down wind screen, rear passenger seat, extra fuel containers, shovel and axe, rear-mounted spare and an auxiliary trailer. The condition and presentation is excellent and will be an exciting addition to any collection.</car>
  <car id="_369106177" price="36300">This cream with red Hudson Terraplane spent time on screen in the popular 2009 Hollywood film &#x201C;Public Enemies.&#x201D; Acclaimed actor Johnny Depp, both well-liked and a many time award-nominee, is seen with this Hudson as the Feds try to take down notorious American gangsters John Dillinger, Baby Face Nelson and Pretty Boy Floyd during the rampaging crime wave of the 1930s. The Hudson is custom in that it has a 350-cid Chevrolet V-8 engine that is mated to a floor-shift three-speed manual transmission. The period feel is all over this car with a plush velour interior that has nicely presented wood-grain dashboard details and distinct white-faced gauges. Additionally the car carries a heater, clock, radio, dual wipers, rare hood ornament and dual horns. The Hudson has been frame-off restored and has been built to drive and enjoy by being equipped with updates to make it more usable. The vee&#x2019;d radiator shell is nicely complemented by chrome-plated, bullet-shaped headlights, side-louvered hood, skirted fenders and &#x201C;bustle back&#x201D; trunk. There is a metal-clad sidemount on the passenger side along with twin taillights, dual mirrors and artillery-type wheels with wide whitewall tires. The car comes with a DVD of &#x201C;Public Enemies,&#x201D; poster-size screen shot of Johnny Depp with the Terraplane, original movie posters, poster board with many pieces of history and documentation plus the cancelled Universal Studios car title. This presents a wonderful opportunity for museums and collectors to acquire a documented movie car that was in a well-marketed film with one of America&#x2019;s best-known and highest-paid stars.</car>
  <car id="_385892097" price="71500">Presented in gorgeous bright red with a tan leather interior, this E-Type Jaguar is breathtaking. It has been fully restored, with great attention to detail, down to every nut-and-bolt. The power comes from a 4.2 inline six-cylinder engine mated to a manual four-speed transmission. It also has an AM/FM radio, chrome wire wheels, tan soft-top and a black convertible boot. The tan leather interior is brand new and simply exquisite. The quality of this Jaguar is without issue and will be appreciated by any European automobile collector.</car>
  <car id="_385892098" price="46750">The launch of the Jaguar E type in 1961 caused an immediate sensation and once again William Lyons stood the sports car world on its head. His radical new monocoque chassis came with a sensuous aerodynamic body by in-house stylist Malcolm Sayer. &#xA0;Over time, experience and worldwide demand dictated many changes in the sublimely beautiful Jaguar E-Type. This culminated in 1968 with the introduction of the Series II. Federal regulations in the USA, Jaguar&#x2019;s most important export market, drove some of the Series II changes. This included revised lighting and the shift to a pair of carburetors in place of the earlier triple-carb arrangement. The well-proven 4.2-liter inline six-cylinder was little changed, although a higher-capacity water pump helped the E-Type adapt better to warmer climates. Braking was also improved, with larger Girling disc brakes utilizing multi-piston calipers. Inside, more comfortable reclining seats with adjustable headrests were now standard. The Series II marked the maturation of the landmark E-Type and made a great car even better.</car>
  <car id="_402665473" price="123700">Offered here is a very exceptional Kaiser-Darrin. Restored over a period of years by the Schaefer brothers of Burnsville, Minnesota, it is the product of extensive research and meticulous, &#x201C;jewel-like&#x201D; workmanship. &#xA0;Before beginning their restoration, Stan and Andy Schaefer compiled a thick binder of information from which to work. Over the course of the project, they added to the file, so that a complete history with extensive reference material accompanies the car, as do 1954 Florida license plates. Although the restoration is now several years old, the car remains fresh and fine, the engine compartment is spotless, and incredible detail and authenticity exude from the entire car. The Yellow Satin paint is outstanding; chrome and trim are excellent, and the upholstery is exceptional. The car comes with side curtains, top and other accessories and is ready to enjoy. The power is delivered by a 161-cid, 90-hp F-head inline six-cylinder engine that is mated to a three-speed manual transmission. &#xA0;Although some 60-percent of production survives, it amounts to barely 300 cars from the nearly 500 built. The next owner will not only have one of the best &#x2013; he or she will be unlikely to ever meet another on the road. &#xA0;The Kaiser-Darrin had its beginnings in secret in the shops of the renowned Howard &#x201C;Dutch&#x201D; Darrin in California. Darrin had designed the 1951 model Kaisers, but fell out with Kaiser management. The car&#x2019;s fiberglass body incorporated the hallmark &#x201C;Darrin dip&#x201D; along the doors, which were of a novel sliding design. To enter the Kaiser-Darrin, one twisted the door handle and pushed the door forward into the front fender. &#xA0;Henry Kaiser was not initially impressed, but his wife was. Through her influence, Kaiser was convinced to put it into production. An F-head Willys six was chosen as the powerplant (Kaiser had bought Willys in 1953), and a few cars were finished toward the end of that year. At $3,668 it was expensive &#x2013; more than a Series 62 Cadillac or a Lincoln Capri &#x2013; but came with lots of standard equipment: a three-position landau top, tinted windshield with washers and a tachometer. Weather protection, however, was furnished by side curtains. Production began in January 1954, but sales were slow. At year&#x2019;s end, about 100 remained unsold.</car>
  <car id="_419452161" price="104500">Lamborghini officially replaced the Countach when it unveiled the Diablo in Monte Carlo in January of 1990. The Diablo was introduced under Lamborghini&#x2019;s brief period of Chrysler ownership, preserving but refining its layout, smoothing out the body&#x2019;s humps and bumps, and improving occupant accommodations. Bodywork was now an aluminum alloy with composite pieces used for the trunk and engine cover, and square section tubing was used for the car's tube frame. The Chrysler-designed interior offered comfort and room that a Countach owner might find difficult to imagine. Power now came from an enlarged 5.7-liter, 492-hp version of the long-serving Lamborghini 60-degree V-12. The blazing red Diablo seen here is the epitome of Italian design. It is fitted with a tan leather interior that is in excellent condition overall with minimal wear only seen on the seat bolsters. A five-speed transmission shifter looks right at home in the sculpted console. An Alpine sound system with CD player is also found inside. Michelin Pilot tires have been mounted on the stylish factory alloy rims. Overall, this is a fine example of the Diablo; the future of Lamborghini collectibles.</car>
  <car id="_436221441" price="145750">The Mercedes Benz 190SL is today what it was when introduced in 1954 at the New York Motor Show: A less expensive, more practical, and smaller version of the illustrious 300SL. However, it is certainly not lacking in any of its big brothers technical refinements. The 190SL offered plenty of capability and race-bred technology to those enthusiasts considering a sporting roadster. From its production in 1955 through its replacement with the 230SL in 1963, nearly 26,000 would be produced with only a fraction in existence today. The 190SL was also the start of the &#x201C;options list&#x201D; for Mercedes-Benz. Never before could a car be tailored like a fine suit the way a 190SL could have been. Everything from elaborate color schemes, tops, accessories, seats, and even a very rare sports-racing option was available. These nimble little two seat roadsters with their iconic, forward styling were the first Mercedes-Benz convertibles to hit home with the U.S. market and started a full-fledged frenzy, and one that has yet to end over 58 years later. The example on offer here, Chassis # 12104010017435 is presented today as a fantastically well-restored 190SL and adheres to its original build specifications. Thanks to The Mercedes-Benz Classic Center and the accompanying Chassis Zertifikat, we know that this example was delivered exactly as follows per its original Data Card: Engine number: 121 921 10 017544 Transmission number: 017680 Front axle number, l: 17650 Front axle number, r: 17634 Rear axle number: 010057 Steering box number: 17492 Exterior color code: 658 &#x2013; ivory Option Codes: 401- Single seats 441- Bumper with guards, front 515- Becker radio set &#x201C;Europe&#x201D; USA 320- Outside rearview mirror, on the left, loose Early history on this example shows that it was a European delivery and by 1966 was in the hands of its second long term owner in California. The original service booklet shows that in 1966-1972 the car was regularly serviced by both Mercedes-Benz of San Diego, and Adams Foreign car service, as documented in the original book. From this point forward there are numerous receipts from foreign car repair shops in the San Diego area that kept the car in order from 1972 until about 1991 where it was put away in dry storage, and driven seldom, until 2001 when it was serviced once more to be readied for sale. In 2003 a Mr. Bob Friedman of Nevada acquired the 190SL out of 40-plus year ownership as the third owner, with restoration in mind. Upon his acquisition, Mr. Friedman entrusted the services of Bell Straus Restoration of Costa Mesa, California to carry out a total restoration of this 190SL to as new condition. As a totally numbers matching example, in good original colors, and with the benefit of being a straight and totally solid California car from nearly new, it doesn&#x2019;t get much better in terms of a car to restore. The fact is this car has always been a good, solid, rust-free and accident-free example, which for a 190SL is indeed a rare thing. As restoration began in 2006 the entire car was completely disassembled, drivetrain removed, paint stripped, and the car was soon a completely apart and a bare chassis. Receipts in excess of $80,000 for services performed entail a total rebuild of the engine, transmission, rear end, brakes, steering and suspension as well as ancillary components. The chrome was completely refinished as new and the car received fresh and correct DB658 Ivory paint. Reassembly included a brand new interior to exacting and correct specifications, down to all of the little chrome items and most minute details. It shows superbly and is easily concours quality. Final assembly included a new and very correct German canvas top, all rubber components and nicely finished with a hardtop and new boot cover. Since completion this 190SL has been enjoyed for only 1,602 kilometers (or about 900 miles) making this a very fresh example with merely break in/sorting miles attributed to it since completion of the restoration. As a nearly new example it is easily eligible for MBCNA events, concours and rallies and can be enjoyed as a well-sorted and restored example with no needs other than an enthusiastic owner. The car starts instantly, runs well showing strong oil pressure and very quick throttle response thanks to updated Weber carburetion (The original Solex carburetors are included in the sale). Going around a corner comes with ease as does stopping and accelerating. Having the benefit of being totally rebuilt throughout this 190SL is indeed quick, nimble and responsive and all-round well-suited for immediate use with excellent road manners. It is everything one would expect from a well-restored and concours quality example. The fit and finish throughout should also be noted as excellent, the body is straight down the sides with good shut lines and panel fitment throughout. The chrome gleams and all of the accompanying rubber pieces are supple and nearly new as well. The glass is free from any defects and the interior is nothing short of new, but also shows as highly correct right down to the Becker Radio. The engine bay is another item on 190SL&#x2019;s that warrants much attention from any discerning buyer. It has been nicely detailed and when restored there was quite obviously a lot of attention paid to items regarding correctness and presentation. Of which no corners were cut and the engine bay shows exactly as it should on a correct and well-restored 190SL. In conclusion, this is an opportunity worth much consideration by any collector or enthusiast who is in the market for a finely restored 190SL. Factor in documented and known California history from new, limited ownership, two tops, original books, jack, spare and a totally documented history/restoration and one has a real opportunity to acquire a concours quality example, and a truly great car. The rising market tide has seen much recent appreciation for the &#x201C;miniature 300SL&#x201D; with no real end in sight. This will no doubt be an opportunity to buy a very good car to be enjoyed, but also will likely prove to be a wise investment as well.</car>
  <car id="_452997121" price="90750">The 1954 Monarch differed from its Meteor and Canadian Ford siblings by following Mercury in adopting the U.S.-built 161-hp, 256-cid OHV V-8 engine and updated ball-joint front suspension. The series was further differentiated with the expansion into two series &#x2013; the base Monarch and the Lucerne which corresponded to the Monterey in the U.S. Styling distinctions included a Lincoln-like front bumper and grille, &#x201C;V&#x201D; hood ornament, floating MONARCH letters, disc with crown front fender ornament, 1953 Ford-style rear quarter molding and crown emblazoned wheel covers. Total Monarch production for the model year was 6,909 units. This orange convertible with matching orange and cream interior and brown convertible top makes quite the impression with its oh-so-&#x2018;50s color scheme. It is equipped with wide whitewall tires, dual spotlights, AM radio, power steering, power windows and automatic transmission.</car>
  <car id="_469776385" price="30800">Owning and experiencing the pleasure of driving a good MGA is a thrill. This 1962 example offers everything that one could hope for in a vintage roadster. As the final version of the MGA, the MK II included an upgraded 1622-cc engine with revised heads, disc brakes and a four-speed transmission. Very clean and detailed, this engine compartment shines like new with the dual SU carburetors and every component in place. The paint and body are just as nice and highlighting the exterior is a trunk-mount luggage rack, Lucas driving lights, wide whitewall tires and quality chrome and trim. An AM radio is mounted in the well-presented dashboard and the black upholstery is very attractive with red piping. In short, this MGA presents in very good condition and can be shown and driven with pride and quite possibly take home some awards.</car>
  <car id="_469779457" price="15400">The TR6 was the smoothly redesigned successor to the TR5/250, face-lifted by the German coachbuilder Karmann of Osnabruck. Headlights were moved out to the far corners of the fenders and a new grille was fashioned. The rear end was lengthened and squared off in a Kamm-style chop with wraparound horizontal taillights. Power was provided from Triumph&#x2019;s torquey, 106-hp, 2.5-litre inline six-cylinder. The TR6 was introduced in 1968 and remained in production through 1975 with U.S. sales continuing through 1976. Over 94,000 were sold with the United States being the largest market for the car. &#xA0;This jaunty blue TR6 with black convertible top and vinyl interior is equipped a four-speed manual transmission, AM/FM radio and alloy wheels. The trim is noted to be in good condition.</car>
  <car id="_486547713" price="62700">Always built to the highest standards, Packard was unquestionably one of the finest American cars of the pre-war era. The successful straight eight-cylinder engine was re-christened &#x2018;Super Eight&#x2019; for 1933, by which time all Packards featured synchromesh transmissions. Packard celebrated 1939 with its Seventeenth Series. They offered in their Super Eight brochure the phrase, &#x201C;For you who want a super car.&#x201D; Yes, even in 1939, the term is associated with fine automobiles. For the days of ever-crowding streets, it was to give the proud owner nimbleness and ease of handling, combined with power and luxury that only a big car could offer. It gives you the smartness of famous and ageless Packard lines, with a distinctive beauty all its own. Don&#x2019;t forget the richness of upholstery fittings and trim, plus the specially-built Packard 130 horsepower powerplant with smoothness and performance in period traffic and a spectacular dash in the open roads of the immediate pre-war years. Offered today is this exquisitely restored 1939 Packard 1703. Introduced in September of 1938, only 3,962 examples, in several body styles, were produced in the Super Eight Series for 1939 and Packard&#x2019;s Seventeenth Series. Among the many features included, you will find dual fender-mounted spares with matching, painted steel covers with pedestal mirrors, rear trunk rack, dash-mounted clock, plus radio and heater. The elegant styling is seen in the vee&#x2019;d radiator shell, bullet-shaped headlights and skirted fenders. This same aqua blue color was exhibited at the 2010 Greenwich Concours d&#x2019;Elegance and still presents especially well since its 25 year old restoration. The tan cloth top, paint, chrome and trim all have been well-preserved and detailed as expected on a respected American classic. Quite rare and very beautiful, this Packard will stand out any event shown, and this model is recognized as a "Full Classic" by the esteemed Classic Car Club of America.</car>
  <car id="_503331841" price="23100">Plymouth&#x2019;s Belvedere was the company&#x2019;s mid-sized offering in the line-up, and as such, was capable of many tasks. It was also noted to be of good size and weight for the performance world and was chosen as the NASCAR entry, driven by the legendary Richard Petty. Equipped with a smaller V-8 than Petty would have used at the track, this convertible is one of only 2,502 convertibles constructed for the year. It has an automatic transmission, console with tachometer, AM radio, bucket seats and power steering. A Kenwood sound system has been neatly mounted under the dash for enhanced tunes. Each area of this convertible, from the engine compartment and interior to the paint and trim, is clean and presentable. As a low production example of the Belvedere II, you can feel proud and confident driving it to any show.</car>
  <car id="_503332353" price="39050">In 1990, Car &amp; Driver included the Plymouth GTX 440, in their &#x201C;top ten musclecars of all time&#x201D; list. Enthusiasts who have had the opportunity to experience the pavement shaking power the GTX produces would agree that this honor is well-deserved. This GTX is reported to have the original 375 horsepower Super Commando V-8 under the hood and is hooked to an automatic transmission with console selector. The car is optioned with power steering, power disc brakes, bucket seats with headrests and rally gauges that include a 150-mph speedometer and tachometer. Factory road wheels are set off with redline radial tires. With approximately 50 miles driven since the full rotisserie restoration, this GTX is an excellent choice for a top musclecar.</car>
  <car id="_503332609" price="100000">This fearsome A12 Plymouth Road Runner is a rare and desirable example complete with Galen Govier&#x2019;s certification, including an overall rating of 1.3 out of 6. The car is described as a &#x201C;very nicely restored, &#x2018;semi-survivor&#x2019; vehicle&#x201D; with 44,000 actual miles. It is further stated that the paint, bodywork and sheetmetal is in &#x201C;great condition.&#x201D; Due to their high-performance attributes, few A12 Road Runners survive today and of the limited number that do, most have lost quite a bit of original sheetmetal and their original engines. Incredibly that isn&#x2019;t the case here. This Road Runner has all of its original body panels. The underside of the car is unrestored, as is the trunk, door jambs and engine compartment. The exterior has been repainted once, and it is very nice. The A12 has an ownership history that dates back until 1976. The car has spent the majority of its existence in Oklahoma and Kansas.&#xA0; &#xA0;There were 797 examples of the 1969-1/2 Hardtop A12 Road Runner built for the United States market. Of those 797, 422 were four-speeds and 375 automatics. According to those in the know, this is car number 95 out of 100 four-speed A12 Road Runners known to exist. This particular car is one of five that received the options found on this car, and it had a late production run. It had a scheduled production date for April 26, 1969 and actually rolled off the line at the end of June. &#xA0;This example is beautifully finished in R-4 Red with Black accents and a black interior. Under the hood is the original and desirable 440-cid, 390-hp V-8 high-performance engine with three two-barrel Holley carburetors (A12) mated to a floor-mounted four-speed A833 manual transmission with 18-splines and Hurst shifter with woodgrain knob and reverse warning light. It is equipped with a &#x201C;bulletproof&#x201D; Dana Sure-Grip rear end with 4.10:1 gears and 9.75-inch ring gear. &#xA0;The special equipment list is long and includes a seven blade torque drive fan, 26-inch high-performance radiator with fan shroud, 11-inch heavy-duty drum brakes, dual breaker distributor, correct Edelbrock aluminum intake manifold, solenoid throttle stop and special engine modifications. Known as the 1969-1/2 &#x201C;M-code;&#x201D; this car is specially equipped with a lift-off fiberglass hood finished in flat black and attached with four chrome hood locking pins. There is a functional airscoop and in this area &#x201C;440-6BBL&#x201D; is proudly displayed, as seen from the factory. This all-business machine runs with G70 x 15-inch Goodyear wide tread Polyglas redline tires that are mounted on 15- x 6-inch JJ wheels stamped with an &#x201C;H&#x201D; between the chrome lug nuts and are painted black. &#xA0;Along with Galen Govier twice certifying the Road Runner, he is reported to have described the A12 as overall &#x201C;one of the best he&#x2019;s seen and very well cared for.&#x201D; It also comes with its original Broadcast Sheet, original fender tag, and is listed in the Chrysler Registry and noted as car #273 in the 1969-1/2 Six Pack/Six Barrel Registry. Further inspection has been conducted by Dave Wise, MMC Detroit Mopar. &#xA0;In 1969 Motor Trend Magazine named the Road Runner the CAR OF THE YEAR. The cars equipped with the A12 package were extremely fast, running 12.91 in the 1/4-mile in stock configuration. We are pleased to present this car at auction and invite you to inspect it for yourself.</car>
  <car id="_503332610" price="34650">Not everyone will recall that the 440 Cuda of 1969 is, after more than years, still simply one of the rarest and highest power-to-weight ratio musclecars ever produced. So, what could possibly best this combination? A Hemi-powered version of the car, of course, is the answer. The fastback seen here has been vastly improved from its original six-banger self with a modern 5.7 Hemi V-8 with electronic fuel injection. While retaining a very stock appearing interior with an automatic on the console, the underpinnings were fully enhanced with custom exhaust, front disc brakes, and rear-mounted battery, along with American Racing Torque Thrust rims wrapped with redline tires. Not until the key is turned that anyone will realize the power that rests beneath the hood.</car>
  <car id="_503332865" price="31900">For many throughout the 60s and into the 70s, a musclecar took them to work all week, to the supermarket and to the drag strip on the weekend. In the eyes of some enthusiasts, the Barracuda was the best muscle car on the block and one of the finest multi-purpose options. Moulin Rouge is the obvious color choice on this coupe. It is equipped with a 383 V-8, column shift automatic transmission, power steering and brakes and a rear spoiler. The bucket seat interior appears fully restored from the door panels to the carpeting. Fitted with modern upgrades, such as Firehawk radial tires and an aftermarket tachometer, this brilliant Plymouth is both clean and docile enough to drive every week day and take to the shows on the weekends. A win/win combination.</car>
  <car id="_503332866" price="54550">The Barracuda was all-new for 1970 sharing its basic E-body with the also all-new Dodge Challenger. The styling was both bulky and muscular mocking the fuselage styling of Chrysler&#x2019;s full-size cars. Though Chrysler was late to the pony car party, fans of the marque today boldly claim that Chrysler saved the best for last. To the delight of musclecar fans, this Barracuda is loaded with factory options. Highlighted by the special impact color of SubLime with a black vinyl top, interior, and exterior tape graphics; this Barracuda is equipped with the 440-cid Super Commando V-8, Shaker hood, Torqueflite automatic transmission, air conditioning, rear window louvers, factory Rallye wheels, AM radio with 8-track tape player, plus power steering and brakes.</car>
  <car id="_520104961" price="32000">Whatever the job, the1950 Pontiac Sedan Delivery was willing to step up and do it in unsurpassed style and comfort. You could have one vehicle for many purposes; whether it&#x2019;s shopping, vacation, camping, or just plain old work &#x2013; the errand could be handled in popular style. &#xA0;Whatever the job, the1950 Pontiac Sedan Delivery was willing to step up and do it in unsurpassed style and comfort. You could have one vehicle for many purposes; whether it&#x2019;s shopping, vacation, camping, or just plain old work &#x2013; the errand could be handled in popular style. &#xA0;The interior is fitted with modern bucket seats divided by a center console; banjo steering wheel and custom gauges, including a steering column-mounted tachometer are additional interior elements. The cargo area of the Sedan Delivery has been finished with carpet on the floor and both panel sides for comfort and acoustics that enhance travel time. Custom paint with tasteful flames and graphics adorn the nicely finished two-tone exterior. Other features to note include the custom sound system, dual mirrors, distinctive Pontiac hood trim, plus modern 17-inch, five-spoke mag-style wheels with blackwall radial tires. This is the perfect street rod to promote your favorite company, or to use and enjoy in a versatile manner, just like when it was new.</car>
  <car id="_520109825" price="140250">The SCCA held its first Trans Am race on March 25, 1966 in Sebring, Florida. Organized as a manufacturers&#x2019; championship for under 5-litre (305-cid) four-passenger sedans, it became the premier motorsports series for American pony cars. Camaros, Mustangs, and Javelins with driver like Mark Donohue, Parnelli Jones, Peter Revson and George Follmer were the stars. Ironically, the Firebird was never really supported by Pontiac in Trans Am racing, yet GM division chose the &#x2019;69 Firebird as the basis for a specialty model while paying a $5 per car royalty to the Sports Car Club of America for the use of the name. The specialty model was introduced in February at the Chicago Auto Show as a $725 option. It included, among other things, the Ram-Air 400 V-8, heavy-duty suspension, power front disc brakes and variable-ratio power steering and the distinctive Polar White paint with blue racing stripes and Trans Am lettering, found on all of this years similar models . This one year only body style has a special hood, fender scoops and a rear wing as part of the exciting Trans Am package. Performance was excellent as this was essentially GTO hardware in a 500 pound lighter package. Only 689 coupes and eight convertibles were produced making this a highly desirable and rare musclecar. This beautifully restored example is a rust-free car with all its original sheetmetal. It comes with its original window sticker and PHS documentation, plus the Ram Air III equipped 400-cid, 350-hp V-8 is original to the car. Wearing the proper blue and white exterior combination, it is equipped with all the requisite equipment including Rally II wheels, Firestone Polyglas redline tires, power steering, power brakes and AM radio; just as it was originally built.</car>
  <car id="_520110081" price="53900">Beautiful example of a 1970 Pontiac GTO Judge. &#xA0;Finished in Liberty Blue, this Judge has it all. &#xA0;The Judge has proven itself as a highly sought after collectible. &#xA0; This color combination is one of the most beuatiful offered.</car>
  <car id="_536891649" price="68750">Default Car Info</car>
  <car id="_553650177" price="46750">From no less an authority than the late, respected Duesenberg expert and author Fred Roe (Duesenberg: The Pursuit of Perfection, Dalton Watson LTD., 1982) comes the background on this unique speedster that was clearly inspired by the styling of the Mercer Raceabout. As related by Mr. Roe, from a letter dated April 1993, this car was built as a hobby by Mr. Lassiter Hoyle in the 1940s. He was an unmarried man that lived with his grandmother and who indulged in endless automotive pursuits from his boyhood until the mid-1950s. He owned, swapped and traded many cars of all kinds. At the same time Mr. Hoyle collected automotive photographs by the thousands and literature just as intensively. The quest for power and speed was very strong in Southern California in the late &#x2018;30s and the formal hot rod movement was just beginning in this region at the time. It resulted in the creation of many outrageous combinations of existing automotive technology, some for competition, others for the sheer fun and the pure joy of creation. Mr. Roe believed that fun and creation was Mr. Hoyle&#x2019;s primary motivation, but he enjoyed testing his creations for top end speed and rate of acceleration. He had previously built a &#x201C;powerful beast&#x201D; using a Duesenberg Model J engine in 1942 that is pictured in Mr. Roe&#x2019;s book on page 264. Mr. Roe believed that Mr. Hoyle was well-aware of the solid movement in the Los Angeles area of the period preservation and enjoyment of pre-World War I antique cars and did not feel that this car was built by dismantling complete cars of their components to build this special, instead he proceeded by acquiring loose parts. The platform is based on a 1912 Regal underslung chassis and a Roamer-Duesenberg four-cylinder engine. Mr. Hoyle had a friend who specialized in &#x201C;playing&#x201D; with old Duesenberg-powered Roamers and either from or with his help, acquired the powerplant. The car was put together through sheer ingenuity that culminated in the car we have on offer. Fred Roe was confident that Lassiter Hoyle did not intend to deceive anyone that this was an authentic factory-built old car, but it inevitably became known as either a 1912 Regal or the settled upon 1914 Roamer with Duesenberg engine. Regal built the model with the underslung frame from 1911 to around 1914, so this is accurately portrayed. There were no Roamers until 1916 and no Roamers with the Rochester-Duesenberg production engine (which the car carries) until late 1919 at the very earliest. So it would be incorrect to claim that the engine or other associated Roamer parts as being any earlier than 1920 or 1921. Certainly the look of the car suggests an early date, and we also know that the car was allowed to participate in activities of the early meetings of the Horseless Carriage Club of America (HCCA). Mr. Roe related that after losing track of the car when Mr. Hoyle disposed of it from his collection; he saw it in Hershey, Pennsylvania in the early 1970s. After a few different owners, it settled in a museum until being made available at this point in time. The car is well-documented in this form and also appears in &#x201C;Duesenberg: The Pursuit of Perfection&#x201D; on page 72. Mr. Roe concluded that the automobile was central to American life in the 20th century and upon its introduction was seized upon by thousands of individuals who thought they could make it better or bend it to their own ideas for its final use. The irresistible American urge to tinker, originate and improve found the automobile a most welcome subject, and this thought and practice continues to this day, no matter the technology. It was further concluded to be a true piece of automotive Americana dating back nearly 70 years. Displaying the Rochester-Duesenberg engine, manual gearbox, Regal frame and tidy angular fenders make for an impressive period piece. Buffalo wire wheels, monocle windshield, motometer, tufted individual seating and many brass components all add up to a very specialized and intriguing car that has a many year, documented history.</car>
  <car id="_570440449" price="49500">Rolls-Royce learned with its Silver Dawn model that its loyal customers were willing to accept standardized coachwork; considerably less expensive than that provided by specialty coachbuilers. When the Silver Cloud was introduced in 1955, it too, was offered as a standard steel saloon by Pressed Steel, albeit with some body panels in aluminum. Introduced with six-cylinder power in 1955, four years later it received a modern V-8 and was dubbed the Silver Cloud II. In 1963 came the final modification to Silver Cloud III status with the introduction of four headlights, a lowered front cowl and bonnet, additional engine power and a myriad of detail refinements. Elegantly painted in maroon with silver pinstriping, this lovely Cloud III has a red leather interior trimmed in wood and features an automatic transmission, power steering and brakes, along with power windows and an aftermarket CD player. Paint and chrome are described in great condition.</car>
  <car id="_587217153" price="825500">The Cobra on offer is the 23rd production example that was built. It was billed to Shelby American on October 1, 1962 and sold to Downtown Ford in Los Angeles on November 28, 1962. Its earliest ownership data is unknown, but from 1971 until 2011, it was under the stewardship of one owner, Ruben Garnica. The Cobra was initially restored in the early 1980s and has recently received a fresh restoration that has returned the car to its original glory. At some point early in its life, the engine in CSX2023 was upgraded to a 289-cid V-8. The engine is fitted with the correct components; including early and correct S1 intake, carburetor and distributor. The Cobra has its cast-iron scatter shield and the engine displays hollow-lettered Cobra valve covers. The four-speed manual transmission controls the shift progressions and has the original style shifter. &#xA0;According to an Auctions America Specialist, this Cobra is in fantastic running and driving order. The engine is well-tuned, providing ample power and resonating V-8 tones. CSX2023 is equipped with AC logo knock-off hub chrome wire wheels with Goodyear Power Cushion whitewall tires (including spare), factory correct dual exhaust system, fresh Silver Moss poly paint, four-wheel disc brakes, leather upholstered seats and soft-top with side curtains. Another original aspect of CSX2023 is that the car has not had a hood scoop or side vents added over time. It also retains its original instrumentation and as further evidence of its early production, is still fitted with a mechanical tach-drive off the back of its Lucas generator. Other desirable features include a Motolita steering wheel, Ray Brown three-inch lap belts, an original Smiths clock, windwings and sunvisors. &#xA0;With outstanding reliability and drive-ability, this is a fantastic machine for many types and venues of vintage racing, touring, road rally&#x2019;s and favorite local thoroughfares. The iconic Shelby Cobra makes a powerful statement on the road, track, or inhabiting your favored garage space. &#xA0;Few sagas in automotive history are larger than that of Carroll Shelby and his Cobra. By the time Shelby approached AC Cars in England in 1961, with the intention of installing a Ford V-8 engine into the beautiful AC Bristol Roadster, the concept of stuffing a powerful large-bore engine into a lightweight platform was nothing new. Between Shelby&#x2019;s marketing savvy, engineering vision and fortuitous timing, this marque became the most successful purveyor of the idea, and the resulting Shelby Cobra became the ultimate execution of this concept. Although Shelby&#x2019;s original purpose for challenging Ferrari&#x2019;s racing supremacy wasn&#x2019;t truly realized until the emergence of the aerodynamic Daytona Coupe and his subsequent participation in the Ford GT40 program, the original Cobra, nonetheless, quickly became a celebrated workhorse of the SCCA racing circuit, as well as European FIA championships, and the singularly most handsome dual-purpose roadster that remains one of the archetypal legends of American racing and sports car production.</car>
  <car id="_587217665" price="214500">Given that it was the first race-ready vehicle ever produced by an American automaker, the Shelby GT 350 was an immediate hit. Each 2+2 Mustang fastback delivered by Ford to Shelby&#x2019;s Los Angeles-area factory was extensively modified. Every GT 350 featured a K-code 289 cubic inch V-8 pushed to 306 horsepower, side-exiting exhausts, fiberglass hood with air scoop, and the rear seat was eliminated. A Ford top-loader four-speed manual transmission and a stiffened suspension rounded out the essential changes. For 1965, all Shelby GT 350s were painted Wimbledon White. At $4,584, the initial list price was steep, but Shelby had no problem selling 516 street-legal racecars in 1965, the first year of production for a legend in the making. Each GT 350 was designed and assembled with the intention of heading off to race tracks &#x2013; which were soon dominated by the high-performance coupes. &#xA0;Rarely are automobiles as sought-after and seemingly immune to market fluctuations as those given Carroll Shelby&#x2019;s performance touch. The Shelby American Automobile Club&#x2019;s World Registry keeps detailed records of each Shelby-modified Mustang made. The Shelby GT 350 represented here is a solid, documented example that was subject to an older restoration of quality. It remains in excellent, well-preserved condition. The car, (SFM5S260) was originally shipped to Koons Ford in Falls Church, Virginia in June 1965. The car was initially purchased by Dr. John Clift of Vienna, Virginia and has a well-established ownership record. The late Carroll Shelby signed the glovebox; a very nice personal touch for one of his creations. The Shelby has blue LeMans stripes and correctly styled Shelby Cragar wheels, including the spare. The Shelby being offered is an easily appreciated example that will not look out of place in any collection of significant performance cars or on any show field. &#xA0;Few high performance cars homologated for road use have enjoyed the devoted following of the Shelby GT 350. In order to qualify for 1965 SCCA/B production competition, Carroll Shelby was required to produce at least 100 cars by February of that year &#x2013; a deadline he met and later exceeded thanks to heavy demand for his high-performance modified Ford Mustangs.</car>
  <car id="_587218177" price="27500">This is a Group Five Cobra that exhibits the muscle and visual features of the original Shelby-crafted design. Underneath; however, it enjoys many benefits of having a proven Corvette design, power, comfort and reliability. The body molds were made from an original 427 Shelby Cobra and split four inches wider and five inches longer, while keeping true to the initial shapes and contours. The conversion utilizes a 1974 Corvette chassis which has been bead-blasted, primed and painted. The entire front end was rebuilt with new brake lines, disc brakes, shocks and a new wiring harness. The original Corvette 350-cid V-8 engine has been completely rebuilt with a new cam, larger pistons with a .040 over kit. This is in combination with Hooker headers, side pipes and slide-in mufflers and now produces around 350 horsepower. There is a new aluminum-core radiator with dual six-blade fans and a transmission cooler. The original Turbo-Hydramatic 400 transmission has also been rebuilt with a shift-kit. Thanks are attributed to Corvette engineering for the car sitting lower to the ground than many similar replicas, and the design will accommodate a six-foot and somewhat taller driver. The steering wheel is tilt/telescopic to assist with the driver comfort and the mahogany steering wheel has the proper Cobra emblem. This is a nicely executed Shelby tribute that is presented in blue with white stripes and a black vinyl interior. Among the desirable signature features found are sunvisiors, rollbar, windwings, dual mirrors, quick-fill fuel cap and Halibrand-style wheels that are mounted with Goodyear Eagle tires.</car>
  <car id="_587218178" price="108350">This Shelby GT 500 was originally completed in late April 1967. &#xA0;This car was first purchased by Mr. James Estepp in November of the same year. The ownership history is documented through the Shelby American Registry, and its odometer registers less than 47,000 miles.&#xA0; This Dark Blue Fastback was restored approximately two years ago and is presented in a befitting manner with a black knitted d&#xE9;cor group interior. This example is equipped with the 428-cid, 355-hp V-8 engine and floor-shift four-speed manual transmission, along with other desirable features such as power steering, power brakes, under-dash ammeter and oil pressure gauges, fold-down rear seat, courtesy light group and an AM radio. The LeMans stripes are distinctive in white and the overall presentation is enhanced by factory Shelby 10-spoke alloy wheels (also utilized for the spare) and center-mounted lights. The engine compartment is correctly detailed and the platform is presented in an extremely desirable configuration. Its appearance in this sale presents an opportunity not to be missed. &#xA0;When Ford decided to make a serious performance Mustang, they went to Carroll Shelby, whose Ford-engined Cobras were setting the world on fire. They sent Shelby a white 1965 Fastback, without rear seats or hood. He worked his magic with the 289 engine, coaxing it to 306 horsepower, and put on a fiberglass hood with a functional scoop. A blue stripe was applied to lower side, with bold &#x201C;GT 350&#x201D; aft of the front wheel opening. A more ambitious program began in 1966. GT 350s became available in red, green, blue and black. During the year, hoods were changed to steel because the fiberglass was proving troublesome. &#xA0;Nineteen sixty-seven brought a mildly re-contoured Mustang body. Shelby took out the grille, and put a pair of high beam lights in the cavity. Taillights were replaced by rectangular units, and air scoops were punched into the side coves, ahead of the rear wheels. But the big news was the GT 500, with the 428-cubic inch engine used in that year&#x2019;s Shelby Cobra. With 10.5 to 1 compression and a Holley four-barrel it made 355-hp. A four-speed manual was standard, but the C-6 automatic could be ordered. It proved more popular than the GT 350, with 2,050 built. Shelby Automotive, however, had outgrown their California plant. At the end of the 1967 production year, the final assembly operation was moved to Michigan.</car>
  <car id="_587218433" price="110000">According to research executed by a previous owner, this Shelby GT 350 Convertible was built on May 22, 1968, and was one of 50 vehicles used as a Ford Executive vehicle in California until June 1969. At this point, the 50 cars were shipped to 50 Ford dealers throughout the United States for sale to the general public.&#xA0; &#xA0;This particular car was delivered to Underwood Motor Co. &#x201C;Fordland&#x201D; in Clinton, Michigan. According to the original purchase order and sales receipt (which come with the car), an agreement was reached to buy the car on June 19, 1969, when the new owner put down $20.00, traded in his 1964 Mercury Comet four-door sedan (valued at $753.80) and his signature to pay the $3,280.00 balance. The Statement of Vehicle Sale from Underwood Motor Co. is dated June 27, 1969, issued at the time of the sales completion. The new owner enjoyed his stewardship of the Shelby for the next 31 years. &#xA0; When the next owner purchased the GT 350 in October 2000, the car had less than 40,000 miles on the odometer, and to his great surprise he located the original build sheet in the car. Now showing just over 50,000 miles on the odometer; of the 4,451 Shelby Mustangs built in 1968, only 404 were GT 350 convertibles. Finished in fresh Acapulco Blue with a black vinyl interior and a black soft-top with the two-piece folding glass rear window; the car is also fitted with Shelby cast-aluminum 10-spoke wheels. Power is derived from the famous 302-cid, 250-hp V-8 engine connected to a Top Loader four-speed, close-ratio manual transmission. Additional equipment found on the Shelby includes overhead safety bar with tie-down loops, inertia-reel shoulder harnesses, tilt steering wheel, Dzus twist-type hood locks, Lucas FT8 foglamps, driver&#x2019;s side mirror remote, deluxe steering wheel, wheel lip moldings; power steering and brakes. The Shelby has full instrumentation, including oil pressure gauge, ammeter gauge and clock. &#xA0; This is a great example of Carroll Shelby&#x2019;s legendary Mustang that helped launch a generation of enthusiasts.</car>
  <car id="_587218434" price="129800">Carroll Shelby, the renegade Texan who built and sold the legendary 289 Cobra, had the idea to apply the Shelby magic to Ford&#x2019;s hot, new Mustang. It was a match made in heaven. However, by 1968, the competition was catching up. Ford executives in Dearborn, Michigan, were getting tired of hearing about the big block Chevelle&#x2019;s success on the national drag strips. They needed to develop a Ford that could beat the Chevy head-to-head. They turned to their old speed partner, Carroll Shelby, to breed a Cobra with an appetite for Chevrolets. Shelby&#x2019;s 360 horsepower, 428-cubic inch GT500 was performing respectably, but when the special Cobra-Jet engine was developed, how could Shelby resist? Thus, the GT 500KR&#x2014;the King of the Road&#x2014;was born, powered by a pavement eating Cobra-Jet 428 engine that was cunningly rated at only 335 horsepower as a ruse to fool the competition and the insurance companies. The engine, in fact, pumped out at least 400 horsepower and 440 foot-pounds of torque. The KR included a number of engine modifications over the 428 Police Interceptor engine in standard GT500s. The Cobra-Jet engine had low-riser heads from the famed 427 engine, along with a beefier crank, rods and pistons. Additionally, the KR had larger brakes, under-hood suspension bracing, and staggered rear shocks to prevent axle wind-up and wheel hop, making the KR the best of the best. This special example is presented in Lime Green Metallic and was delivered new to Courtesy Motors, Inc. of Littleton, Colorado with a base price of $4,472.57. Its Invoice #05226 confirms that additional options, which took the final price to $5,431.21, included power disc brakes, shoulder harnesses, a fold-down rear seat, an AM pushbutton radio, a Select-O-Matic automatic transmission, Selectaire-air conditioning, tinted glass, power steering and a Tilt-Pop steering wheel. Further items found on the GT 500KR are a rollbar, aftermarket AM/FM/cassette stereo, foglights and Shelby 10-spoke alloy wheels. Additional paperwork includes the broadcast sheet and the Shelby Automotive, Inc. 1968 Cobra GT 350/500 Individual Order No. 4383, dated July 1968 that also confirms the cars lineage. In 1968 Shelby accounted for building 4,450 total cars. This uncommon example is one of 933 GT 500KR fastbacks and presents very well, remaining an unshakable testament to the legacy of Carroll Shelby and his fabulous cars.</car>
  <car id="_587218945" price="59950">The updated GT 350 of 1969 introduced a number of stylistic and mechanical changes and, like any good car, a touch of drama. The GT 350&#x2019;s new engine was a Windsor 351-cubic inch V-8, registering 290 brake horsepower. Cosmetic changes included a new grille, hood, side ducts to help cool the engine and rear brakes, and an overall body length that grew by four inches. Ford handled the redesign work of the 1969 GT350 themselves, giving Carroll Shelby little input. As a result, Shelby pulled his contract with Ford in the summer of 1969. With this in mind, Ford wanted to keep consumer interest in the GT 350 alive, leading to some corporate mischief. Ford sent the 788 unsold 1969 Shelbys to Kar Kraft, the aftermarket shop that assembled the Boss 429 in Dearborn, Michigan, to outfit them with hood stripes and a chin spoiler. Ford made these modifications in 1969 in order to avoid an upcoming federal law that required the installation of an anti-theft locking steering column in 1970. Upon leaving factory grounds for a third time, these unsold 1969 Shelbys were given new VIN numbers and data plates for 1970. This orange with black GT 350 fastback is nicely equipped with factory air conditioning, factory Shelby mag wheels, rear window sport slats, fold-down rear seat, racing mirrors with driver&#x2019;s side remote and an aftermarket AM/FM radio.</car>
  <car id="_587229697" price="173250">This exciting Shelby Cobra is one of fifty cars produced by Shelby American to honor the golden anniversary of the iconic CSX 2000, the first Shelby Cobra ever built and one of the most valuable sports cars in the world today. The 50th Anniversary Limited Edition CSX 8000-series Cobra has exclusive use of CSX serial numbers 8950-8999. This particular car is the fifth built, being numbered CSX 8954 and features a Black hand-laid fiberglass body that is greatly complemented by leather seats and wool carpet in Mercedes Wine. This is for all means a &#x201C;new&#x201D; car with only 60 miles driven. The car has a tube frame that supports a hardy mechanical platform that includes a 289-cid, 350-hp V-8 engine, five-speed manual transmission, Shelby aluminum housing differential, dual piston four-wheel disc brakes, rack-and-pinion steering and Spicer split-spline half-shafts. The cockpit features Stewart Warner gauges, tinted windscreen visors, leather-covered dash and map pockets, unique 50th Anniversary floor mats, Shelby harnesses and wood steering wheel with a limited edition horn button. The glovebox lid is auto-pen signed by the late Carroll Shelby. The front grille is instantly recognizable, and the car looks ready for action with front and rear bumpers, windwings, chrome 15-inch wire wheels and unique front, rear and side 50th Anniversary badging that is finished in a gold tone.</car>
  <car id="_603991809" price="42900">Studebaker started its second century with a completely new car design. Styled by Robert Bourke of Raymond Loewy&#x2019;s design studio, the 1953 Studebakers are arguably the most stylish Studebakers of all-time and a high point of automotive design. The low, sleek lines were in contrast with anything else on the road at the time and very European in look. Despite the handsome styling, sales unfortunately continued to decline. &#xA0;Featuring a custom silver exterior, it has a red leather interior featuring bucket seats, center console and custom dash. Power is supplied by a V-8 engine and automatic transmission. In addition, this &#x201C;Stude&#x201D; has power windows, CD player, dual mirrors, tilt steering, detailed engine bay and custom wheels in the similar style of period Halibrands.</car>
  <car id="_620764673" price="40825">In 1902, the first Triumph motorcycle was produced, designed by Johann Schulte, using single-cylinder 2.25-hp Belgian Minerva engine with automatic inlet valve and battery/coil ignition, fitted onto a bicycle frame. The following year 500 units were ordered and sold; a resounding success. By the mid-&#x2018;20s the company had moved into a 500,000 square foot facility, employed 3,000 people and could produce nearly 30,000 bikes. In the era of this bike, the company hit financial problems and in 1936 the Triumph motorcycle businesses were sold to Jack Sangster of Ariel to become the Triumph Engineering Company. Triumph Motorcycles is the largest and longest-running British motorcycle manufacturer. In fact, it claims to be the oldest continuous production motorcycle company in the world, despite its numerous setbacks. Its ability to endure has earned the brand iconic status. Proudly offered here, this 1936 Triumph 500-cc 5/5 stands as a testament to the superior design, mechanicals and marketing that Triumph used to create an empire. The 5/5 is described as the top 500-cc overhead valve model in its range, and it was also classified as a 'Mark V.' This Val Page designed bike was proclaimed in brochures to be the source &#x201C;for faultless riding.&#x201D; Fully outfitted, it has Euro license plates, exquisite black and burgundy paint with gold stripes, plus it is equipped with a folding windscreen and auxiliary headlamp for the side car. The full restoration leaves nothing to want as the motorcycle and side car are museum quality.</car>
  <car id="_637543681" price="66000">According to the Krause, Standard Catalog of U.S. Military Vehicles, Second Edition; only 2,877 M16 halftracks were produced during 1943-44. This example has been restored in a complete &#x201C;nut-and-bolt&#x201D; manner that is also period correct. The White has a detailed replica 50-caliber machine gun that audibly fires with propane gas feed.&#xA0; The armored halftrack is powered by a White 386-cid NOS flathead six-cylinder gasoline engine that produces 325 pound-feet torque with a top speed of 45-mph. This fearsome military platform is reported to be complete in every detail, right down to the 1942 Michigan license plate with the 1943 metal addendum tag. There is a complete picture history of the restoration. &#xA0;With rubber tracks and operational front winch; the White is parade ready, including period camouflage netting and canvas top.</car>
</aoCars>
